Ah
Well guys
Guys I mean
Really want everyone to be able to participate
Okay, how are you guys doing? Yeah, we're trying. I'll get along. I mean
Hey, hun, how are you tonight? I'm good. How are you good? I
Was sitting here listening kind of half asleep like
Come on guys. How many times does this man have to tell you?
Stop saying stupid ass words you were grown-ass adults stop it
Yeah, I don't know somebody wrote in chat and I repeated it come on now
I'm sitting here listening site. I felt like you were teaching a kindergarten class
Yeah, I'm so bad for you. I'm like what the fuck this man has repeated himself. I don't know how many times
like
It's a little bit crazy, you know, you know, so that's why you know
Here we have only have pages here. Let's add a page page
Hi, how are you I'm good. How are you good love page? She's a sweet lady
Hey, I did I didn't see you tonight page
They have a DMT pen.
Cool.
Have you ever done it?
Oh my god, it was crazy.
It was just like, it's like so crazy.
It's like so strong.
Like, I tripped like three times.
The third time was like,
not as strong as the first two times.
We're like, oh my god.
What is this you took?
DMT DMT DMT is like ayahuasca, but it's like, you know in the more it's a different kind of different form
It's a little bit different than the is it hot or no
It's a it's from a it's from a it's from like the Acacia wood or like or from a wood called mimosas still is it's actually found
that it's that it's naturally producing in your brain and it
Releases a lot before death usually and people have hallucinations and things
But you can extract it from certain woods.
It's almost in every plant, but it's the strongest
concentrations in a couple of woods.
You strip it from the bark.
And then you put it back in the pot.
But it is so it's like the it's like the strongest listen. It is really amazing. Wow
But I was like sitting like I was like sitting like with my arms twisted and like it's like everything was like
It's like really crazy trip. Did you have to go somewhere like?
No
They brought it and also and then his girlfriend like clean my whole kitchen. Oh my god
She like like scrub my floor
She just like there were shoes there were like she wanted to like help me clean and get my house good
But she cleaned my kitchen and it looks so good and so
I know you've been working so hard and it's given me motivation because you know
I need to clean out like closets and some of our stuff, you know, just declutter and
Just start donating. I donate a bunch of stuff anyway to nonprofits, but
I've got to work on that. I've got to start decluttering more
Yeah, well, I think now we're not somewhere yet, but you know, I should have I should have some spring cleaning
But yeah, I have but I've so many cool things to like bring out and show like the chat
I feel that that I haven't like brought out if I have a lot of stuff to take sort of my bedroom
And I just had a few stuff all the stuff that I haven't been showing I brought out here last year
So I have like tons more stuff to bring out a lot of cool stuff. So I'll unveil more more
There's gonna be
A lot more I'm gonna do a lot more terror on this show. I'm gonna probably
try to do like, you know six five to six days a week
And I'll try to do like four to five hours the stream and I'll try to try to
Reserve the first hour of the of the stream for doing a general terror reading for
the chat and the you know the viewers and the panel and then or the chat and the viewers and then
And do any private readings or anything or three readings to and then have the rest for open panels and other stuff. So, yeah
Yeah
Very good. Yeah, it's like it seems like it's a lot calmer
I just modded everybody then there's not gonna be you know people be people going after other
After the mods and they yelling at the mods or yeah, you time me out
You know, there's so many people just like I said, and now also nobody can time anybody out. So it's kind of works, you know
Best way it's you know, so you don't have to worry about anybody coming you out
Right. Yeah, I was kind of glad because I got tired of you know having to defend myself
Why I'm following your rules
Yeah
And but everybody it's like and it was nothing it was nothing like nobody did anything wrong
It was just I it was for like basically everyone's protection because you know
We're getting a lot of a lot of people in here and you know
There were kind of a lot of people a lot of people complaining about mods asking for mod and stuff like that
It's just easier if nobody has it, right?
I
i can moderate mine certainly hopefully and it was actually today it was on for several hours
it was just like i was the chat was like absolutely perfect there's like i don't think there was even
one troll comment right all that so all of a sudden it's just like even putting good energy out there
because i get you know new intentions you're like okay you're just kind of like a fresh
start deleting all the deleting all the all the mods and everything and then
so it feels good because no one's gonna get bothered anymore and then i'll i'll basically
But if I miss if there's some comment or something that has dogs thing
And I and I miss it or something or the needs to be
Deleted or if there's a comment about somebody that they don't like to comment
You know, and I don't see just bring it to my attention because there's a lot of chat and stuff
So there was some when I was here earlier today. You're right. It was much much
Pomeran that one individual made some nasty remarks about me and my animals
So I blocked them and yeah, that that's just not excuse. That's just
People will sit in it and they'll tell you know, they know that you know kicking on people and the animals their loved ones
It's like that's like a love. It's like this. They just know it's just sort of annoying basically
But you know, that's not a lot of my checkers. Let's let's not do that
Yeah, exactly, but like yeah guys, let's like, you know, and I think also pages
I'm like, you know, I just realized that you know how it feels to like have someone
kind of call your names on the panel because you know some people call your names or you know kind of mean on the panel
And it's like and so so I realized you know, but I felt I feel like how I know how other people the panel felt when I
people were calling them that and
maybe like you know
People wanted me to step in or something and so maybe maybe I didn't step in and kept going and stuff like that
So I'm gonna I'm gonna be more
We're careful to make the panel safe. I'm not gonna let anybody be attacked on the panel
I guess I got a lot of good advice from some other streamers and so yeah
So proud of you because you're definitely better than that
I love you got all the stuff that it takes to you're already doing it right you're doing it
You're doing a good job, but you can definitely
This channel can grow and grow and grow and grow and it's going in the right direction. So just keep up the good
And I'm really proud of people having just a mindset switch and just kind of saying that you're going to go with a different kind of flow.
We can still have fun, but like people do have to be respectful, especially if, if we've all got pretty good relationships with each other for the most part, you know.
but and it's like also like but it's interesting like one side I got into like an energy of like
Down an energy of boundaries rather than like an energy and like I had an energy of like
Oh, I'll just forgive anybody anytime for it right and it's like, you know, but I just had enough of like, you know
To burn too many times. So it's like now I feel like good about said boundaries and make the nobies know and
and but then you know be be a
diplomatic and kind of got to refuse something but I don't
Don't let my kindness be taken for weakness because then people will just walk all over me, right?
I think denison gave you some really sound advice. Yeah
I'm not a long time and he he does not put up with any mess in his chat. So
No, I don't don't like that shit. Um
I said I try I don't like that either like it's okay like a certain there's certain places that it's acceptable
and we can all go have fun and play but there's certain places that you know
It's just I don't play on my channel when it comes to that as far as handling spirit because it's not only you know
It's disrespectful to everybody involved
I think it's like I go almost like a free speech thing like oh can't you have free speech?
He's on youtube like obviously you can't break teo as
Yeah
Exactly well, I mean and there's we had rusty like rusty was on the panel last night and
And then and then you know
It was because we were talking we were talking about all this other stuff and then rusty came on and like, you know
See I'm man. Oh, see I'm a comes on home and he I'm Sammy uses like, you know, and I gga which is like I think if I
Don't think it's I think it's kind of okay
But then she's like she's like well he can say and I gga why can't I say and I gg er?
And then I was like, yeah, and then they're like,
but you're white, you're white.
And she's like, I still can say it.
It's my right to say it.
Then she started talking about Trump.
But yeah, she was kind of funny, but yeah.
You can't even say the C-word anymore brother when it comes to that word
I really feel like it matters on who's saying it and how they're using it. Yeah
Yeah, yeah
I was gonna say when you say things like that necessarily the algorithm will pick up the word and so and so it's like
Make up a new rule listen, no, no, no that word saying on your platform simple as that
You don't
By the way, you actually, I know you you brought your little buddy over here that broke the rule
He's your little homie. Oh hate speech like it's right. What are you talking about?
I brought somebody I didn't bring nobody
It's not acceptable it's his channel. That's how it's gonna be. Let's move on
I mean if they can't do what he wants him to do then knock him off the fucking panel
So for one time I actually
Like listen, if you're a channel owner or you got to do state the rules to people that may not know
Yeah, yeah, yeah, they would have been in the beginning and listen if they fuck up they okay
You got to go, you know
Out of what the rules is because they may come from a different community with other words being said
Because you've been told many times
Because I actually know you
It was a little bunny that you co-signed for by the way, which I asked
Let's not say my friends and my buddy. No, you can play it back because I asked you to co-sign. You said, yeah
No, because I know who he is from another panel. That's all I'm saying. I know him
I thought that came I can't I think he moved here with you or something
He's not
He when he says something he doesn't mean
You can say certain words. I don't give a fucker. He's racist or not, but he can break the TOS. Yeah
The adult thing is, it's not because anybody's like,
it's like anybody's like really offended,
because it's because like we live in like a little like,
you know, the world is like a little bit more piecey.
And then, you know, so people, you know,
even if the AI doesn't pick it up,
people can like be offended and flag it.
And it's like, I just don't feel like dealing with that.
It's just because it's just bad for the,
I guess the terms of service have racial language,
Oh, it's so offensive to anybody
That was pretty much the only word I was guilty of saying so
I try to you know adjust that
Adjust that into my vocabulary to where I could say something different whenever I want to say that word, you know
And I really never meant it as
I know
You're a punk. Yeah. Yeah. It's no it's no offense. It's just like, you know, it's another one of those words
Yeah
Go see
He gets it he gets it he gets it goes like we can drop them
Everyone's like, you know, I started DMC and I was like
I was like, yeah, it's crazy. Oh
Hey, oh, this is just dog guys in the chat. That's how you're in the chat, right? I've seen you in the chat
Yeah, Alexander, yeah, you're doing here
There's no fucking Alexander
Yo charisma fall back you can't talk to me unless you ever get on pen
Well, bitch, I'm on panel. You want to run? Not you fuck you. I'm talking about charisma
That person right there took it. No
You can't talk to me unless you ever get on panel then you talk to me fam
And then what are you gonna do to ignore them or block them like what are you gonna do when they burn that?
My life ever
Oh Lord, what would you like to talk about mamma since you don't want to talk about you don't want to debate or nothing
But you're not a good debate or what do you want to talk go ahead? What do you want to talk about have the floor?
What do you want to talk about panel your own you do this and you argue with people just have a conversation
About what? I mean if I disagree I'm on a disagree. It's okay to disagree
But you're sitting here arguing with
About a comment he made about somebody in chat. I mean let it go. Yeah
Going on I can yeah, go ahead
It's been like 20 minutes. We shouldn't we keep it off the labor on like, you know, it's like we're gonna say I can just say
Yeah, okay. Thank you so much. I
Want to have a nice happy family. I think we're I think yeah, I think you know we can
You know, I'll get along and we'll give a nice panel of five people. How's everyone doing so?
Okay, you're laughing. What's so funny page?
You left them out
Just don't
Are you gonna kill us?
Well, no, I don't know what it's called. I keep forgetting. Okay, that's okay. She's literally always hard
Yeah, I literally am and it's not your life. So you're fine. You want to have a debate?
Didn't make an argument again
People smoke weed we chill relax. Maybe you should start living would you like a mission? Maybe you should pick up a joint
No, yeah, I
My friend gave me a little bit of weed tonight. It's a little bit bad. Love you. It's okay. We love you. I don't think you
It's a thing. Yeah. I'm not trying to be rude. I just think. I said you're always high. Are you not always high? I mean, I'm not trying to be rude. I totally am. These are facts. Okay, you're always high.
You're always drunk, so there you go. And you're, you know what? I would like, you're always a retard. Would I say that about you? I wouldn't. I'm not that rude. There's nothing about me that's the R word, okay? I have more intelligence.
Okay, sorry. It's the D word. Dumb, dumb.
I'm sorry. I used the wrong word. I think that's you don't go so I think that's you
Psychi just said move it on but if you want to debate it's like he gives me a wish and we can debate
He said move it on. Well, it'll need to be I don't want to be like the TOS or something
That's that's to do it like you know, just
Go ahead. Yeah. What do you want to do? Do you ever said that I debate so totally different? Yeah. Yeah. We're gonna talk shit
Let's run it. I mean let's stay stay turns. You ever do you have a topic to propose?
If he got a topic that he would like to debate on I
I would take any single topic, whatever he wants to talk about.
And I'm not going to debate about a way.
Okay, you have a topic?
He said you get to pick.
Go pick a topic.
Yeah, I got a topic.
If you're not a designer, why the fuck are you
every night trying to debate me
when you don't know what the fuck you're talking about?
There's my topic.
You're still talking over me by the way. Go ahead. Go ahead. That's how I would do that on top again
You don't be smart. Let's just think of thinking of like an actual topic and he'll do a debate
I'm not gonna do it because you guys you guys aren't debate
No, I understand your question
I'm trying not to break anything I'm trying to be from me on the YouTube
Topic shouldn't break to your words. Just bring up any random
Argument for him
I promise you we can he can't
Stick to one word
Pick a topic, okay. Yeah
let's
It better not be and elaborate on it. Let's hop it. I don't want to get into the shit
We're always getting into that something
Let me talk to you. Let me talk to you. Shut up. This is called
conversation. My name's like you. It's called brainstorming
and because we're all up here on a panel, entertaining people
who are also involved in the conversation, we should probably
add something more to it than you think. Okay. You know, I'm a
little bit more open minded than that. Okay. So, this is why I've
never I don't want to debate. I'd rather have a full
Well, yeah, I agree. I was just trying to test him right quick because I know he can't debate. He just told
Well, no listen if we're gonna agree with shit like we don't
Let's all agree to something you're not gonna you know better can traffic can that suggest the topic?
or debate. Yeah. Okay. Good idea. That's a good idea. Okay. Okay. What animal has had a spiritual
meaning to everybody in in here? Okay. Okay. This is Hogwarts. This is Harry Potter. Or just
yeah. All right. This is like, this is like sharing a, you know, that's what, it's not a good
You know
They can operate very well like
Especially like if they're like that if they're like an alpha they can lead a pack
But also like if they're like a lone wolf
They still have that wolf instinct in survival. You know, they know how to eat
They know how to fight, you know, I mean like they they can stay in the ground. They know when to lay low
They're smart the intellect here now for or you're alone with whatever you were like that little bitch in the back
You know, you're the 13th one behind. So like so well, you're that little bitch behind
There's no pack animals. I'm sorry. So pack animals, but you're the 13th one. You're in the back of one
Sorry, I'm sorry
I don't know if I'm sorry
Are you sorry for it?
But yeah, but you know wolf it yeah wolves are I don't all the dogs are all descendant from the gray wolf
And so you know all dogs are you know just yeah, and so is like you know a wolf
Wolfs are you know they can be also, you know, they're very loyal like like dogs in a pack animals like dogs and
Yeah, but we just
Yes, sir. Yes, sir
How are you guys? What's your favorite? What's your a toad of animal?
Do you like a a Wolverine or a honey badger? A Wolverine or a honey badger? Okay ghost
What's to be the honey badger? I think you know, okay, are you done a badger too?
But I'm tougher than all of y'all like my logic will fuck all of y'all. That's how I like all your ass
Okay, wait, so tougher or smarter because that's very that's too
I'll claim both of them. That's my claim
So you think that you're tougher and some on you. Yes, you're on this thing. I
Would have I mean I have to take a double
So you would be yes
Walking out of a cave and if anyone this is three they're welcome to join and fucking debate me
Guys this your big pipes is the backstage. He he and we're bombing the other night. What do you think we should let him back back on?
Listen
Mm-hmm. Mr. Big Pipe's okay. His name is Mr. Big Pipe's you go listen there
I would say let him on see how he does if you're in the mood to kick him off if he gets out of hand
Okay, okay
Okay, hello, mr. Big Pipe's are you having a better mood today?
Yeah, you know
Like I was really drunk
very very and then
You sure what you're you're poking at me. You were poking at me. Well, I mean, I was like, yeah, I mean, no
I was we had finally, you know, you played like, you know music for a couple of hours and you know and then
Yeah, it's like I don't want to like that's gonna happen when I'm when I'm the drunk like
Now you're gonna see I don't want to I don't want to do that
It's gonna have to be mr. Big brother. You remember you don't remember when you said you asked me
He said you want to make out with me, and then you said I
Did you say my breath like fish and take a shower and remember when you said that I don't know what you smell like
I know you do. Why would you say that I wouldn't take that seriously like okay?
Why'd you say but I might even say my breast milk fish. How do you know?
He did say he was strong, which I don't know why he said that but are you gonna do it again, mr. Requites?
No, I'm trying to chill. Okay, so it's so good
So I key I would let him slide about you. Well for the I mean I think I think I think he apologized and he said he was
They never really I was able to get it you know deleted before
I knew Dan, but you know my
You know
He's saying a Beatles song for two hours
Yeah, but McCartney, what was the song
And then Mr. Big Five started yelling, but his microphone went out at the same time, so it was like 2% yelling in the background for like an hour.
And then when he started yelling, he was getting frustrated.
I know.
We're getting your microphone.
I think it's hilarious when I do that and I don't realize it.
I've just gone off for a while.
Wait, do you do that?
I do that sometimes, not very often.
Well, I've I've known you for a while now, and I've never heard you want to do that. No, it takes a lot
It does it takes quite well. All right
It depends. I guess I don't know on the person like Michael fucking stupid linguine. He can just fuck off all the time
Yeah, I hear he's a huge. I mean, I haven't seen him for a while. Oh, well, he's a complete dick, but you know
Mom
You know, I see people with like, you know, pet their dogs and stuff and like, you know, I know people
Like he's booze were never
Never lost more than yet my band. No, no, no, no big the HK though. It was like he wasn't bad
He was not he was there wasn't a donation to ban
It was just me. I'm like me saying he's banned because I was like I'm mad and then I like
Then I like it was so and it's already been over 24 hours in the way, so he didn't he was banned over to my throat
So don't it's okay. Come on. Come on. Come on. Memphis safe
Okay, I've never said the data for over 24 hours. Yeah, this is over a day since he was on
I've literally apologized to both those people and then okay
Like I'm over it and you guys keep bringing you offended me brother
But yeah, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm crying now. I'm page page. You can't save me. He has to apologize because I'm fucking upset
Do I get an apology
Well
Okay, first of all you do hold on you uh you band you band them for and I let it back for the band
Oh, my god. Why are you getting
a song about you? He's not going
to play. He didn't do anything
wrong. You didn't know you. Come
on. He didn't remember anything
about you. Please stop. Oh, I was
feeling really sad and he sang a
very sad song and it kind of it
did trigger me and it hurt me
and then you did give me a card
that I was going to feel sad later
and I think it's his fault. So, I
think you should apologize.
Mr. Big Pipe, do you want me to draw a picture?
Do you want me to draw a picture of you, Mr. Big Pipe?
Yeah, go for it.
Okay.
I did some pictures of people in chat, but yeah, I think I showed them a few times, so.
Oh, okay, I'll drop this in the comments and we'll not drunk at a sink for fuck the
30 hours.
I mean, God, man.
Do you get hungover?
Like, you can even more hungover from exerting that much energy while still hungover.
Oh, and you guys are, yeah.
You deserve to hangover.
We're gonna get the jelly now.
It's definitely the jelly's coming in the pic now.
Hey, what's up, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, I mean things. Can you sing it's off to goes Pete's a serenade goes please? All right
Here there you go, there you go
Yeah, do do that. Can you sing I got you
Joining
Yeah. Yeah. I can't. I can't.
I
Yeah, here's a custom share we got
Bitch you're gonna make a claim. Let's fucking debate. You kept quiet
Gentle spoke
I'm so much you're fucking lot
All right, go ahead because I'm gonna bring that
What are you talking about my pay what
No, no, no, they came up with a good proposition psyche said that that person can sing sonny you can sing shit
Yeah
Yeah, yeah, Google shares vocals for that song I want to hear you share it shows boys
and I want you guys to do it. Yeah, it was certainly until he tried to debate me. That's what I'm not doing. Guys, do it for my show, please. Just do it for my show. It'll be everyone will love it. Everyone will laugh. And in a good way. Everyone's already laughing. Hold on. Yeah. Yeah. Who will love it? That's how I love it. I can't even say it. I can't even sing. I like that.
I mean page was the only one that like I'm like actually made my mind up, but no, I'm not doing now. No, I'm trying to yeah
No, it's not debate the thing you're sure you're sure you are sharing share is you
Sing
I literally just told you I'm not going to do it, so I don't know why he did it.
They say I don't want to pay the rent
Before it's all our money
That's all that's been
Okay
Alright, next one down down
And there might be two
But I got you
Doesn't matter
I got you
Baby, ask them like
I'll be share I'll be share. No, it's not. You're you're Rudy shares part. Oh, I
Think over the lyrics, hold on
Let's do it again. Mr. Bigfoot. I'll see you along with you. Let's start with the
They say our love won't pay the rent part. Okay with the part where you sound like a shit
Hey
I
Can do that I got you big part, okay
They say what are y'all is that right? Oh, let me want to start
Okay, I start or down go for it. I'll just keep playing it. Okay
Okay
And we don't know, we won't find out until we grow
Well I don't know, if that's all true, you got me and baby I got you
Now together Mr. Big Five
Babe, babe
I got you babe
I got you
Got you
Okay
Beautiful those beautiful that's perfect. Yeah, thank you. Yeah, that was pretty we say
We can't get any better than that
We got we got a perfect word. That was a perfect for us. That was it flawless. So I'll go where'd you go good ghost?
Okay, good ghost disappeared ghost ghosted us take a shadow
Okay, well, I have my hard lemonade. I also have, what else? I have two more, I have two more harder lemons. So I play hard lemons.
It's like my candle is like raspberry hard lemonade or something. Look, it's made in a, what is that?
There's an American flag on my candle. Made in a...
Oh my God. Is this made in America?
That's a candle. It looks like something tasty. Can you drink it?
I said that earlier and I shouldn't have said it out loud. I was like, I really want to drink this candle.
Yeah, well, I can imagine that.
Mr. Big Five, don't forget the candle and they smell really good, but you'll be pooping out a candle too.
I don't know that like that would be the worst of the outcome that like that'd be one of them
But that you'd have to be mindful of but they're probably way worse internal issues from drinking. Yeah, I mean
Besides like you'll break burn your burners in mouth and inside this
You know, wax all over you.
You don't drink candles, kids.
What if you drank hot wax and then you pooped out a complete candle? Wouldn't that be amazing?
Well, then you'd probably make millions of dollars.
Yeah. Millions of dollars.
And has Carol's channel, I don't know.
Yeah.
It says specifically on there, one of the only rules on this candle is do not consume it.
Yeah, and do not you don't poop out a candle
Of course you don't consume my guys. No don't know. You know, it smells good. You know, there's really okay
Oh, it goes, you know that uh, it there's a really cool candle that the anime convention
They look like ice cream and they look like you can eat them, but there's there's wax
But uh, hey goes do you want to apologize to the room for what group for ghosting us?
Ghosts, did you ghost us?
I don't gain ears because you're muted
Okay, well, so that was your day. I got you my dogs. Well, let me answer the fucking
What I like to bother you with the train that was going to buy and my also my dog's team out was barking
Why would I bother with that? What were you a train you're gonna buy you you made trains that?
No, I'm just kidding. I'm coping. I didn't like the shit. Yes. Are you okay? Are you okay? Are you okay doctor?
Are you okay doctor? Wait, what if I can't do it? I
Just admitted I just didn't like the same way trains
Okay, I
I do your train said mr. Big Pipe's give a train. No, I just I watch a lot of videos on
Are you do you watch Thomas the Thomas that?
No, I'm never watch it
Oh, it's pretty good. But actually I was just getting suggested like vintage toy models like people putting them together and shit
I think it's like the autism
I feel like that. Yeah, you gotta like, you gotta touch that. We can't, well, yeah
Yeah, apparently I do. No, I don't. I don't know. Everybody is on a spectrum of sorts in their own way.
Paige, you're not. Paige, you might be on the spectrum.
Well, you might be too. You might be too. You might be too. You just, you just mask it better.
Well, we'll be together.
But the you know what the definition of a spectrum as it goes like a spectrum means like zero to a hundred
Everyone's on the spectrum everybody is at least at a point zero one, right?
Okay, okay. Yeah
I'm on the spectrum my face
Yeah
I'm zero point zero one on the spectrum
that
He had he said that sexual values on spectrum shoe. He says no one's like a hundred or most people are not a hundred percent or a hundred straight or a hundred percent gay
He said there's a there's a spectrum and so what so where do you guys think you on the
100% straight
If it was like a thousand I would be a thousand okay
Oh
We were talking about the system autism. Okay, yeah, he just
Was
Yeah, I just say I can utilize it and you can't even like like
You can't follow dialogue
Nobody wants it because
Hi
Okay
A little more rarer than you like you to fucking stupid you know the conversation what do you want to talk about let's run that bitch dog
This is an autism. This is like
What happened? What happened?
What's going on everybody?
Gatti's in the building. What's everybody doing?
Those dumb noises
Thank you. Yeah. Oh, it's I enjoy the beat the summer. Oh, don't feel bit
Drag you down 6 a.m. The sub is gonna run. Yeah, I know one up one on here, but you're lucky, brother
Y'all the dumbest is come out of ghost mouth
Love it. Thank you
Puck Puck Elf. He does have to Puck Elf. He does have to watch the show a little bit, you know
Goes is like fat with the glasses and he got a comb over like he he looks weird like he looks like he just
You're also
So that's why you join here because you know better. She could never
fuck around with a guy. You look like you're right here.
So happy. Yo, why don't you come out and let's out of your mouth.
Hey, what's your argument? You're my argument. You're going to have the
debate. I can't slob on to your beer.
I
Did a picture of ghosts here, so here's ghost I did a picture
Oh
You are we got the dumb dumb that's go
Back
Captain Gontu's fucking little partner the one that's like I'm literally debating them
Do you do on a page
Don't know
No, hey psyche real quick real quick. Yeah, like actually real one serious thing. Hey check the score real quick check the school check the school
And 34
134 to 3 4
Yeah, who's winning bitch? Yeah, I mean this is like guys. I drew the page before I have to fix the page
There's one I started doing these and it's not very good to my new lost the page
No, I have the page, but I I need to
Fantastic by the way
You like it. I think it's working better. I think we're better. Yeah, good job, man
Hey, this guy's this is guy this guy. I can't make an argument. So I'm gonna talk shit like dark man. I'm here
Dumb fuck. Let's run that
The fuck you suck about let's run that bitch
You fucking stupid to have it I mean I understand that's all right
Ghost you're not crashing out
Not crashing on at all. There is people that are too stupid to have the government station
Would you like me to crash out?
I'm not I'm not crashing out
You don't know how to crash out
I'm letting you know you don't know what the fuck you're talking about
I'm talking about the stuff I'm talking about
Bro, you're not doing that
Hold on, I don't like to hear myself talk
I'm not doing shit for you
You're not winning any arguments you dumb fuck. Are you really that stupid?
You've been just talking about no nothing except arguing for a bit 20 minutes, so let's talk let's go on to the new topic
So do you want to see pages picture? Here's page. I think a little bit
Oh, wow, that's perfect. Look at that.
That's the smile totally
We see the okay, leave it alone leave it leave the
She's baking a fucking cake to stay turn she's baking a fucking cake to stay turn
you got to use that as you're having trouble. Stay trying. Hey, you're his thing. Who is that one next to it?
No, that's untrackable. Untrackable. I have that. Let me see if I can find it.
So, you don't want to do that. So, you should. Hey, uh, Saki, real quick. He should come see to me
and he should apologize to me because I'm here to hang out. He should come see you. He should apologize.
No, you really don't care. Okay, so it sounds trackable. Here's untrackable and I got I also do
That's his garland. I'm here. You're the track
That's
I
Need to be a little longer, but that's that's perfect
Cheers and guys I also did I also did
Yes
Did you see Texas Scarlett?
Oh, just pitch for it.
Yup.
That's a laugh.
Okay, thank you guys. Yeah, I'm gonna have to crash up. I did Alex. Yeah, yeah, I'll show you
Okay, don't okay, don't crash out of my you get tuned up here
Like
You're not a good debate. You're not a good debate. You're not a good debate. You're not a good debate. You're not a good debate. You're not a good debate. You're not a good debate. You're not a good debate. You're not a good debate. You're not a good debate. You're not a good debate. You're not a good debate. You're not a good debate. You're not a good debate. You're not a good debate. You're not a good debate. You're not a good debate. You're not a good debate. You're not a good debate. You're not a good debate. You're not a good debate. You're not a good debate. You're not a good debate. You're not a good debate. You're not a good debate. You're not a good debate. You're not a good debate. You're not a good debate. You're not a good debate. You're not a good debate. You're not a good debate. You're not a good debate
That's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a demon, that's a
Yeah, you get the privilege of all but you don't like other shit, but can we all talk?
Yeah, we can all talk
Can we can get we think we are the world we can all sing at the same time
Can you play can you play we are the world we can all sing together none of you none of you deserve to sing that shit
I want to know of you. Yeah
We are the world literally literally not one. Yeah. Thank you. I love when I love when you say
Answer the question
I know
Answer the question why
For psyche and page
to
All right, not for us. Okay. Just go ahead and sing it.
Hold on.
No, I can't.
You guys.
It's Jolly.
It's your cue, Esso.
You'll get Jolly.
Yeah, you're gonna.
You are.
Yes, I know it's a bit like I would like I think
I'm gonna say you're a man if I was just for you and
Okay, so I had to join out to your drawings, bro. There's got to be
Hold on wait, how'd you like them? How'd you do the drawings? You know, it's got to be a way you can make that Alex's profile picture really
Oh, yeah, you like the ox one. Yeah
If you don't take a screenshot right now, you know, that doesn't like him
Listen, you should definitely try to make that your profile picture, bro. Yeah
We are the world or
that's perfect
that's cute
you got the head dead on
yeah
I thought it was a good one
I thought he drew Michael Jackson
in big lips for some reason
and broke
let's know we are the world
Clearly.
It's a bit...
No
We all are the children
We are the one to make a brighter day, so let's start together
There's a choice
Making saving our own lives
It's true make a better
day just you
It's that crack head shit the fuck out of here
Okay, what that was a bet actually that was pretty good
You loved it
They all want to make a brighter and it's about to start giving
I mean, it does sound like Will, you know
There's no choice but making it
In every other love
Except to make a better day for you and I
No, for you and me, for you and me
You can do Michael Jackson's part.
There you go. You got it. There you go.
I'm thinking of...
That's so stupid.
That was beautiful, man.
I don't know that was beautiful, bro.
I don't know that long.
I got a tear in my eye.
You got a tear in your eye.
Do you think that if we drink our own tears that maybe that's the fountain of youth, you know hard to see that sometimes
But yeah, but I don't know about that
But you know that like the sad tears and happy tears like you put on our microscope
They have a good different camera for the guy different composition like the you can tell the difference between hatched that here's happy tears
Like different of you does never get in the old way. Oh, this is because come on
Is that impossible?
Big five. I'm just kidding. It's a big five. I'm just talking to you and you're vernacular. It's a big five.
I don't know, I have fun, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know
Yeah, yeah, your arrow is pointing right into his mouth
Yeah
Yeah, I feel like I'm playing Pac-Man. It's time for people to get a bottle of the battle of the bands. Yeah, we
You know
And there are what are
There are hormones and sad to their hormones and sad tears. So it's sad tears. You the hormones come out
It's that it's that a bottle of the battle bands, okay?
Live battle the band. Well, I mean, it's like I mean I have like a I have like a drum
I like a drum like that. I'm gonna bust out the painting drafters
Oh my god, there's a reason why crying is a cleanse to the soul
Hey, I just want to work guys guys women in the chat. You might want to like duct tape your panties
Mr. Panties
Almost I'm just that name stick. I'm gonna call mr. Panney's
He was warm, he came around like he was dignified
Showed me what it was to cry
I didn't laugh! I used to laugh!
Congratulations!
Thank you!
Thank you for what your heart is for!
I don't know you anymore
Nothing's fine, I used to lie
Situation has gone dry
That's what's going on
Nothing's fine, I'm sure
I'm a lot of fame
This is how I feel
I'm told that I am shit
Lying naked on the floor
Illusion never shit
Into something real
I'm wide awake and I can see the perfect time
So you're a little late
I'm already torn
Ooh
Aw, I got chills
How old are we in this on this channel I'm 44 I'm 44
You're my you're my you can do it 45
It's okay
I guess we'll have you a battle of the the battle of the bands maybe next maybe this right here next time
The bands
Mr.. Big Pies you can start for a band called mr.. Big Pies and the panty droppers. I would thought that ever reach it
You don't have to be a what man?
Bullets are goddamn
Yeah
Hey, she played a tambourine
Johnny's and penny droppers sounds kind of cool. Oh
Pays in the mr. Big mr. Mr. Pani. I'll just whistle
types mr. Big panty
Mr. Pan
I was trying to incorporate both of you in the room
It was funny. I was just thinking about something so I was like here for a second
But I wasn't and then I just started laughing out loud and realized you guys didn't even hear it
Now I look nuts and I did not just tell you about it, but that's crazy. See you don't hang out with me. I'm weird
Yeah
You're okay. I know we know Mr. Big Punch. We said it before. Okay, so you're chilling. I mean it's like we're trying to chill.
When you say that, we all start going, ooh, what?
Well, it's like, I want to emphasize the chillness.
Just chill then.
Don't, don't, don't, don't. Okay, Mr. Big Punch, Mr. Big Punch, don't try to chill. Just chill.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Okay, no, you're not laughing at my jokes, Mr. Bigby. It was a joke. I'm from California.
So if there's something bad about me, like how do I improve to be better?
No, no, it's it. It means to be friends with us. What is it?
It's like I don't compare myself to other I want to compare myself the person who wasn't good
She said you're always trying to chill and you are you said it
No disrespect. Mr. Big Pipe's is not good
So I don't like compare myself to other people like because comparisons like the thief of joy it really is
But I want to compare myself to myself
To this person who wasn't good 15 minutes ago, and how can I be a better person? Can you tell me well?
She didn't say you're bad, but she just said you're not good
Hey Tiffany and wears t-shirts, but he could have said bad, but she said she said not good
And so it's maybe some more neutral
She needs to block out the criticism
If you're gonna go on like the full open panel tour you're gonna have a lot of people saying boo, you know
People are just ruining the chat there's a root to everybody so
but if you don't have any
if you don't have any
right
so help me
compare myself to that person that wasn't good
15 minutes ago
but you said you don't want to compare
you said you don't want to compare
I'm comparing myself to myself
comparing myself to myself
You don't have to do that, you have to do that because you are yourself.
That's how I am for that.
Rock out.
It's the big prize, it's my head is big.
Are you a musician?
I agree with that.
I agree with that. That's good advice.
That's real advice.
That's actually legit advice.
You know rock me, I'm a dame.
I'm a diss I'm a diss. Yeah, that's what I was asking for like all that other like hysterics wasn't necessary
I'm a diss
Rock me. I'm a dad. I'm a dad. I'm a dad. I'm a dad. I'm a dad. What do you think you get?
I heard a pretty cool rap song. I heard a pretty cool rap song on Armaday's and you know, it was fucking bad that song.
Dr. Zez. Dr. Zez. Dr. Zez. You go to a Big Pikes concert, you get what, about 20 minutes of music, maybe an hour and a half of criticism?
Yeah
Solid Mike
25 minutes of him 25 minutes if I'm saying he's trying to chill and there were jelly
It's a big five. It's a joke. It's a joke. I love you. I love you. That's a 35 minutes of self-moving. No, you just it's all criticism
Actually super talented, I mean, you know
Guitar banjo or harmonica that he plays he plays them well, and so it's like
Cool shit
You see mr. Bigpipes you're getting some good feedback on the panel tonight, right? Yeah, just chill them
No, I'm too
35 minutes of self-loathing and misery
Yeah
But I'll be I'm being a dead ass to your hill Tony, bro
Thank you. I want to see mr. Bill. I like the mr. Bigpipes smiles. He's a little little a little grin. He gives to me
like the devil
I'm being lazy with like the monitor. I can use like the
Nice microphone or the computer. Well
Unless I had it hooked up there OBS
Yeah, Linda you did because I use the OBS plug-in for my
my phone
camera
I don't think so. I don't think so. I don't think so. I don't think so. Okay. We need to see it. So, are you just going to squint forever?
Yeah, I need to get readers. I think I need to get readers. I am I usually don't wear I've laid sick
But it's like my now my my nearsight and this is kind of
It's like, I don't know. It's kind of like a little bit. Oh, it didn't work, huh?
It did. It was 25 years ago. I had it. So I mean, it's been good for until
After after six months of YouTube, I'm going blind and my my beard is turned white
Thank you, thank you acting like he's never seen
It's like the avatars are really small on this on this device. And so I just
And sometimes I'm sometimes I'm very drunk and I
Forget but I'm trying to go back out. You got a big face, man. Don't let your
And this side is completely turning gray and some of it is white
Shocked
White
Wow, I just say baby face
Yeah, I still have no hair in a gray hair is my head. I'm so thankful having had a hair, but
Um, yeah, I think I'm missing it. I got no hair. I'm bald. Thank you. Yeah, your balls
Yeah, you naturally bald or you shave your head? I'm mobile. Oh, no, no, I say no
I say my head long before long before I started I figured my I was gonna be like my dad be bald by the time
I'm like 26, so I just be involved for 20
Is that a dog?
Oh, it looked like it looked like a lot to
You guys do holy shit. Yeah, they're why
Holy crap, thank you guys for this
He's cool looking though, I like that cat did you do to that cat?
Okay, guess what might guess what my monkey snack is let's play trivia. It's uh, it's like the cool ranch
Fritos who ran something that is so far off
Oh, you should get Nutella and cool ranch Doritos
Nutella beef jerky beef jerky, okay, I'll give you a hint. I'll give you a hint. It's easy, but it's hard
I made it for breakfast today and then froze them because they're easy access if you want
Wapples?
Wapples
Okay, you can freeze them. I make them and fresh and then I freeze them and put them in the freezer and then I keep to pop them in
the toaster or in the microwave
Canadian freezer food
Weird question, but maybe a turn what after the Eli's channel did it come back awesome?
Also forget that one
Today but like
Oh, he got other videos on there, but for whatever reason there's no panels on there
Something going on then with the panels
Dude, I'd be the the furthest one to tell you I have no idea. I don't know how none of this shit works. I'm
Yeah, I didn't
Hey, let's play trivia.
everybody
Somebody got some man. I don't know what they had the channel before but they took the whole shit
He got it back, you know, maybe like three days two or three days later
But this one is weird just
This video is that still there, so I don't you know, I don't really get it. Oh my god
He'll fix it
it will get it back. It is what it is. Whatever happens, he'll fix it. You're right.
Ooh, look at the pancake.
It's dripping.
Yeah, I hit the back button like 80.
Hi, Brian King. Good morning.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
You ever have fruity pebble syrup? That shit's so good. Yeah, I love fruity pebbles. Yeah fruity pebble syrup. Oh my god
But that shit is like the best cereal like in the world
As a man like but saying just saying oh my favorite cereal with fruity pebbles
Oh, that's great. Yeah, that's good. It's good. That's it, Bobby. Bro. Hey, yo, have you ever had a yo?
Have you ever had a fruity pebbles? Um edible?
Like oh, yeah, like a rice crispy ball, but it's edible. Oh, what's really bad?
Yeah, that's really really good
Fine. Oh my god. I'm just head to
We should just
Y'all we can have the ladies doing the lemonade stands, you know, I mean it could be THC lemonade stand
I don't know how you guys can have a conversation about that.
I don't know what y'all are talking about, I don't smoke weed.
Mr. Big Pines, what would you like to speak about then?
Like, focus on something, tell me.
Uh
Okay, but you're just you're whining about you use like during the conversation or like
Maybe I need headphones
I'll play a song.
Go ahead.
We're waiting.
There's soundtrack, man.
I was kind of working on, like, the intro to it.
We're waiting.
I'll just bust into the fucking panty drop.
Yeah, do it.
Yeah, I'm waiting.
Hold on.
Let me, uh...
Yeah, do it, bro.
Do it.
Any day now.
Sometimes God's little ad-libs are funny.
We have to go now. Let's do it
It's like he's working on a song real time, right?
I wish you would sit back from that
You should learn you should learn this song called the truth by Prince
Okay, I'll look up. I
That was freedom. Seriously. Your guitar will go great with that song
Oh, Mr. Big Fives, look at that Prince song.
Because the truth by Prince is more of like a bluesy type song, your shit will be great.
The best song.
Oh, I love that song.
Oh, God, how do you know?
I know you've been high when you're feeling low
When I hit the road, you're missing home
Pulling out your love when you let it go
There you go
I forget
And at the bottom of the glass, open one day, you'll make a dream last,
to turn slow, and I go so fast.
You see it when you close your eyes, so maybe one day, you'll understand why everything
When it starts to snow, all I know is love won't let go
When it doesn't hide, when it's in the love
All I know is love won't let go
Linda dropped her panties
You see that?
They turn they turn it's all out. Okay, you know what mr. Big
Oh, I don't know I had it muted. I'm just back now
We're just back back here, not good
I'm trying to say put what was the feedback now tell me now. I can hear you
Linda says he loves he loves the guy singing
She loves the body or she loves the body and
You got these four panties
Yeah, it's like I didn't really have like I don't know. I was probably like two-thirds confident
So because what if what it's like you you like blow off so many panties that they start suing you for like for damages
I mean, that's why I give the disclaimer like hang on to them or cross your legs if you're not wearing any
Wouldn't everybody start getting public nudity tickets or indecent exposure tickets you that they could
It's like if you were sensitive to like flashing lights and you had seizures, it's kind of like the same type of deal
Okay
My ability
Perfect perfect now exactly same
Like for legal, you know, it's a disclaimer. Okay, Raven wants to say something come
I told you
Got somebody in the back
Um, no, we don't I think I got a reason what you're doing
I
Got that song stuck in my head. I know lady Linda, which one the painting dropper
Yeah, no Linda Linda she left
I mean, it seems like Paige like like she's like I hope that the disclaimer was good enough and you're not trying to sue me for
Yeah, I mean it's like have you ever seen the Matrix the second Matrix movie
Yes, the best one that's the best movie of them. Yeah, we're the guys like he does the thing to that lady in the club
And this is like
And guys guys guys if you're wanting to tap mr. Big Five's apologize about yeah, so I gave him giving you another chance
It's not like do that kind of thing again. He was very drunk and uh
You know the panel thought to give him another chance. Okay, so we kind of take a vote. Yes. All right sounds good
Let him in whoever it is. Let him in. He's here. He's here for the chats kind of thing
Oh, well, you think you're gonna kick him off. I didn't tell you to kick him off because I was mad because he said the Edward like ten times
Like and he was angry at me, but then he apologize everything's good. All right, cool
Oh, okay. So, man, now, so Mr. Big Pipe. So, um, so, so, Doggo says, hey, Pipe, thank you panel and chat. Whoever is
speaking, it was great. Okay. So, you're very good. Thank you. That's positive. Positive. Oh,
slow as hell. He's talking about somebody that's here right now.
Yeah
People are saying like oh now I have this on my head and then it's like damn I influenced
Like it's not me that it's like I'm influencing songs, but even when you guys like
Repeat things that I say like just saying like oh you're so jelly or calling people dorks and shit and knowing that like
That people are like repeating like my catchphrases and shit it does tickle me a little bit every time
Look we just all grow on each other. We should stop hanging out. I'm out time
Fucking totally you
Like you froze
Pipe you play the jug too
Majorly in a serious way, you know
Yeah, yeah, yeah, there you go
Yeah, I don't know how to do it though. I'm probably gonna go a real challenge. We should all find the rat
You know how I fucking rock out, man. I rock out with my cock out, man
Get some spoons
I've had several sets of spoons and
The last two music festivals I went to I gave my spoons away my percussion spoons. I just gave him a way to
I gave him no I gave him to a dude. I gave one of them to a dude. I give another to this lady this like
Lady was
I thought you could use any spoons
No, they were spoons. They're percussive spoons like we can look them look them up on Amazon. They're like 15 bucks
Oh, yeah, I've been using kitchen spoons all these years
I mean, if that works, I'm sure.
Good enough.
Yeah, I don't know. I just like I
learned about the spoons like
Last year some shit, and then I bought two sets of spoons. I gave them away
So now I need to get another set of spoons they're fun to play with you slap them on your leg
That's what she said you are. That's what she said. They want to play with you, aren't they?
We love playing with you.
Oh, here we go. Now it's time.
I can't breathe.
And she doesn't really know how to play it, so it just kind of hangs out in her room and she thinks it's cool.
Just gotta bang it. You just bang it a little bit.
Shake it. Shake it and bang it.
While he plays.
Little a little more than that
Can you blow blow the harmonica and bang it against your head at the same time
I just thought this was kind of cool.
Yeah.
It's cool, baby. It's cool. As long as you can blow it, it's cool.
I wish I had a tambourine. I don't have a tambourine.
I think we got that from my friend who's in a band.
He's very sad.
He's like, here, here's this instrument.
He's like, I don't know what to do with it, but I'm not sad anymore.
That's where they collect the money.
I was going to play two of these, but...
I should learn how to play the harmonica better.
You probably have a C harmonica, which is the one I have right now.
What kind is it?
Hold on, let me look at it.
I don't have you at home.
This is about to bring some harmonica from like 1979.
I have a harmonica from like 1934.
Oh
I was going old with 1979
Dude, this all right, so this harmonica I got is from it just says 1930s is a guy that sold it to me
I could probably actually find that year, but it might be like reducing but it's from germany too. I got a nazi harmonica
Oh, yeah, not not. You got to not hear harmonica.
Hit the blue on that shit. Holy shit. Is that pre-World War II?
It is. It's the 1930s. Hohner harmonica.
How's the condition on it? It's been like already done in the
shit. I don't know. That's it.
So it's probably like three different harmonicas, but the one stamp is why'd you find out that Hitler blew on that shit for a light?
I see baby
I remember when I first started learning about like page what did you do with your harmonica?
I think we're all right. Jesus. We've all been breathing the same air as Jesus. Just get some spoons. Get some spoons and it may be a fork.
A harmonica from Hitler wouldn't be. I think it's so good a sport set.
It's a fork. This is going to plug me. A fork, like for camping. Oh, it's going to be a scorcher this week, shit.
I'll think about where it is, but I'm not going to be able to find it right this instant.
Just that page straightener here tonight. No, I didn't
Are you serious you didn't
Fucking way. Yes, it's very straight boring. Holy shit. How?
boring
I want my hair to be straight. I mean, I think my hair would be like it wouldn't lay that straight
Well, I'll trade you hair then because it has lots of volume and every girl wants volume in their hair
You guys can watch your face in your asshole with the same bar of soap and you go out and you just like
Watched it watching my what do you mean?
But also the statement that I didn't know that was right.
But just to let you know, we washed our face before the asshole.
The face is first.
There you go.
You're looking better.
The face is always first.
That's the way.
That's the way it should go.
Get a big day for that.
Basically, we've done from the top down.
Top down.
From the top down.
We're just telling you the dollars for each thing
that we have to use in the shower.
And then for every little thing that we have to use when we give you
Well, I'm not sure what I just played. I'm gonna see if Amazon has a specialized ass-washer
I would like every apartment I've had I like I always put a bidet in
Hair down now done no, it's not gross at all. It's fucking awesome
Yeah, you got a bidet you got you got water shooting up his fucking ass. So like every time he takes a shit
All right, that will only happen if you try to poop while the water is spraying on it
I could have with my whole life without knowing
You're a free animal
It doesn't work, right? That shit doesn't work. It's spraying shitty water everywhere. No
It's fucking spring water in your ass. Oh, yeah, it's clean. It's rainwater in your ass
What are you doing in the shower? What are you doing in the fucking shower, dude? Holy shit?
I'm not I'm not taking you look up to the hot water to all right. You can adjust you can give it a little
Jesus Christ. All right, if you're really trying to the shower in argument against
You're projecting and being delusional and weird
Dude, you're talking about the days, you're talking about shy words, you're talking about
Chittin' in the sky, we're like, this is body washin' weird.
That's it, like, yeah, get busy. Use some soap and water, man, in a rag. Make sure you got a rag.
Hold on, me and I can work on the intro.
For a long time.
How about the rainbow connection? You know the rainbow connection?
Yeah, uh, Gotti, Minnie Manson performed that on the first appearance on my show.
Oh, that's a great song.
And also, I and this guy, too.
I don't like that song.
What's that?
Nah, we don't fuck with that song yet.
I only know you've been high when you're feeling low
The road when you're missing
Lighters are in the air, people will fuck out
Our lighters go out
Like we tried between the fucking
The Holy Spirit Symphony
We blew the fucking fire right out
I like that guy
Bring your fingers
Oh the long one
You know a bloody Sunday by you
Is he in Daito?
Daito.
How did you do?
It's the same chords.
That was Daito, right?
What the fuck is this? Why are we allowed to be told right now?
What the fuck is this?
Fuck this.
Hi, guys, we're having fun, we're having a concert, a free concert.
This is a live concert, because we don't get to spend the day.
This is free. Free. You want your money back?
You're gonna do a U2 song and they still haven't stopped what I'm looking for.
That's the only one I'm looking for.
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
I hope no one is recording this
It's for them
Big guys, you're so loud
Big guys, you're very loud
Who's moaning?
No moaning
I said like I was about to start rapping, but I was fucking rare. Okay
A rap to this song would be so
Opposite money I was saying like I'm about to rap
I was I was moaning too. I definitely don't miss those days
90s or the rappers
My drake used to do it all the time
I know you're lying. Oh
I made this deck and I forgot about it and I thought it was index cards because I had it neatly packed and like with a bunch of
And then I just found the bunch of them and I'm reading them and they're really fucking funny
She makes her own
Tarot cards my fucking pigs
And no, but these ones are like just my lamest ones. These are like an outline. She's a pro man
Imagine making your own that gangsters. Oh, that's crazy
You're not buying this technique. You're drawing them yourself. That's cool.
Yeah, draw little pictures on it. I do. I have other ones that I've like made with lamination in it.
These were a rough layout of the ones, some of the ones I made. Make a Alex in my PD one, like like a
psyche dude.
The goofy ass, Alex.
He ain't in the steps
You're supposed to be cheating and deceitful. It's fun. Oh yeah, cheating and deceit
Tango
I thought it's a cheat then GT that would that would be that would be cheating because it's like
When I made these are made them for someone who was upset at a time
They're cool
Ghost ghost ghost ghost to be like if it goes left I said he only goes to that and then everyone left
Yep on the flip side it says crash out
Yeah
Yeah, I can add that
This is a cool thing about these custom cards. You're gonna
Right crash out the other side
You got the dumb dumb card
All the dumb dumb card
Nice, you gotta have the dumb dumb card. Yeah
You do have some nice handwriting
He got the dumb dumb car. This means you're a dumb dumb
Don't make me crash out
I can never take those seriously he's a he's a fucking comic to me man
I'll understand why people take him seriously. He's hilarious to me. Yeah, he's a loser. He's a loser
He's somebody you you can't take serious like it's just funny like everything. He says it's funny
He's a joke he's a he's a walking joke
You know, he's really a genius right
the
And just damn well you didn't you know you muted it like halfway through. I am you do I
We wanted to have it just have that in the background because we were all talking a little bit
No
like, like, like, like, like like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like,
Okay, I have a really really really fun creative idea. I wish we should get everybody in here
We should be done everybody. We're here. So we should do this
We can take these because I don't remember what's in them and we can make it someone's card
Or whoever we think of it like we just did this one or we can or have blank ones
And we could make cards for people
That's how that card creativity comes from. It's like it's just like making music or like an art piece, you know
We have to give the card a name and we have to give the card meaning, right?
Yes, but we're gonna look through some of these ones probably and we have to stop
Well, no, we're just gonna read these ones are a little different because they're just kind of like a
Like a basic like a blueprint even if you will building a house but game
How can you be so cold, who's that oh
That's flirty is that you flirty says a cold-blooded got a flirty flirty says that all the time flirty is the one
pretty diamond
Yeah, flirty says how can you be so cold you never heard of say that?
That's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a, that's a
Talk to me be so cold is flirty. We got dry diamonds on it. You can keep talking. I'll just
I mean, I don't know who that person is. I just heard the name and there's somebody said they you know, but
You know transformer and this and that I'm like, so what's a man? I
Mean you think about flirty diamond the name is
But you know
Just like me like you know with a dick of some balls like no
She plays boys like basketball and baseball like he's more than meets the eye
Yeah, but if we Emma's captain of the football team and you know
Has triple D. She was against the sun back
and then multiple
okay backflip queen
the multiple choice
flirty
dusty was a
backflip queen
no backflip queen
oh flirt
and
where does
fucking alex call her all the time
it's funny it's not rude
where the alex
oh um
You know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you
for your story a little beat the beat of three burrito a burrito a burrito of diamonds
Well read all that's how I was as we go for a little
diamond burrito
I mean like I don't know who I'm talking to but this sound like they could have lobotomies
But they could also be like like long-haul truck drivers serial killers for 30 years. I'm excuse me
But we're talking to mr. Bigfoot
Who are you talking about just like getting the vibe. I'm getting you're saying we sound like a body be patient
No, no the other guys like but also like serial killer like if they were like
They were like like long-haul truck driver serial killers for like 40 years. They had like
Projecting
To be on a truck on the road, you know, I do want to be a truck driver. Oh my god. I'm all right. Hold on
Okay, so but you don't so what am I right about the projection about what's what it was about picking up?
passengers and putting them in the trunk
Never
Okay, never okay, but that would why would you or is the long pause doesn't long pause for that. Yeah, it is bizarre
You have to think of it. You have to think about that for a few seconds. Okay. It's bizarre. Never mind like I'm mostly ride motorcycles. It's like
Guys, I think Mr. Big Piper's is a serial killer
That's a stretch
You might not remember like a werewolf
I disagree. I disagree. Okay miss. Okay. No, I was just kidding. I was not. No, you're not
Not a serial killer. I was just because you said you guys sound like serial killers at the bottom is and I said
Well, are you projecting do you want to be a truck driver? I mean, yes
All right
I was talking about what he was doing.
I'm sorry, Mr. Big Pipe.
Mr. Big Pipe, Mr. Big Pipe.
That's a big pipe suppression.
All I'm doing is SNL the Californians
doing the California accident on the Californians.
I'm a Californian.
It sounds like Mr. Big Pipe's
but it sounds like East Coast though.
I don't know, it's very confusing.
It's a big pipe.
Sorry.
I'm sorry, Mr. Big Pipe.
I'll be mad, Mr. Big Pipe.
I don't know. I don't know.
People said
So Q went on the RV like a week after I got in the fight was saying and he went on there
I don't know. I don't know.
Calling people dorks and they knew because I like I took a piece of paper
and wrote dork on it for 20 dollar donation and stapled it on my leg with the staple gun
that these fuckers couldn't figure out how to use they're they're so low IQ they couldn't figure
out how to they bought this they bought this staple gun and they bought the staplers for the
staple gun but they couldn't figure out how to fucking use it i looked this fucker for like
five seconds and it says like load this way into the fucking shit i'm like holy shit stamped into
Thing the dork thing to my leg. Why would you fucking do that? Why?
Like there's content
Staple guns
$100 for it $100 for it like fuck it. I'll do it
the
Oh
It's just saying with like a staple gun to his cheek
I said it put that in your cage bird the cage. Yeah, right?
Oh my god
Unfinished business, it's not business wrong. I know I
Sure did okay, and then there's these ones too. These are so random
I don't know what I was doing when I made them like I'm trying to place myself in that
She's supposed to get out of control. This is psych's channel or any of our channels
Yeah, sorry page finally. All right, Paige. You have my attention. I'm watching
Yeah, I
Missed it. Don't need rewind. I want to see the I wanted to see the controversial
They're all kind of that's why I'm not showing all of them
So I'm finished business mr. Big fire. You're writing down your comments right now like what you think no
She's making cars with a I made this deck like a long time ago, and I just found it in this box
He's ready to every comment in the chat. She's putting on a flash card and she's gonna just read them
I was he's doing no, no, no, I'm finished business
We're against your heart rate, your heart rate.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Okay.
Come on. Are you okay? Are you okay?
You've been really down. You've been really down.
You always think everyone feels better.
I've never even made you smile.
You're completely irritated.
No, I'm just reading. I'm not irritated.
Okay, okay.
Okay, okay. There you go.
I thought you smiled.
Okay
You should have been using these cards all the time every time there's a fight on the panel
Just smile, you know
Well, you know beat it. I think I think being in our talking so everything will be okay guys
I have people a lot of people today. Yeah, tomorrow is a different story and then back and forth back
Hopefully we can get going upward trajectory. I don't like fighting
Let me get a card
Like this one says, I don't know what to do
Celebrate either. I don't know what the fuck to do. Okay there. Okay. Got it. That's on you. You don't know
Here is it for God he hears
I'm always soul searching
Okay, okay, I searched for new souls here. I'll shake off the haters
I got something in my eye
Collecting souls
I'm collecting souls
Yes I am
When you pretend I'm blinded by all your lights
Oh when you're around
Oh when you're blinded by all your lights
That's a good one, sister
I just want a steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak, steak
Don't keep the same
Take it off shake it off
Where's the get out of jail free cut
And a place hey hey hey
I'm just gonna shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake
It's gonna be fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake, fake
Oh
Care of your shit
You can't stop, you can't stop, you can't go around, you can't stop, you can't go around, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you can't stop, you
Oh, awesome divine is that work here? Yes always
Take my breath away
First site hmm on the always like a heart
You like I did I love your style in your vibe. Thank you
Thank you. Yeah, yeah, he said thank you. He said thank you
Now I know now I know now I know the narcissist dude. I'm seriously trying to
All right
Hey, I just un-muted this shit, and I thought it was a fucking cool message. What the fuck?
No, that's good. No one's taking part of you.
Yeah, that's good. We're just having fun.
Don't be insecure. Don't be insecure now. Don't be insecure. Come on.
Like, honestly, like, I don't know people that would say, like, even joke about a shit like that.
Mr. Big Five, it's like, wait, it's like, it's like, it's not even like, remember when you were saying,
oh, I was like, lady, people.
Remember you're safe remember remember you say I think you'll threaten you and it's not like that and then this is more serious
Whenever he goes, oh my god, that's more serious than people
I don't know
Please just chill. It's weird. It's weird and so you guys are like
You're just mimicking thank you
I get to go like that
The big pie stop
I'm sorry. I can't stop. I think my voice has changed. I'm not trying to talk like that. You change my voice. You're very influential
Like you can make fun of me if it makes it feel better make fun of all of us
Yeah, he's like yeah, I say I say the page. I'm not gonna make that page
It's not juice the other though, how can you make you can't make that he can't make someone
Page is pretty close pretty close to perfectly perfect in every way
We're all
Practically perfect
Okay, how's the Gobbador Amanda? Hey Amanda play some blues man. It says don't want to say anything
you
Oh, yeah
Thank you is tuned into a fiddle
Fiddle diva Valley girl. Oh my god. I gotta get a fiddle and I'll do
I'll do a ballet girl
Think of how like fucking marketable I am. It's like all right
Yeah, the valet girls the fucking teagirls love me the fucking hillbillies the bikers love me
You mean the teagirls are teagirls of the trannies, right?
The teagirls love me, brother. They might be the other means transsexual, right?
I mean like I
Why why would they love you?
Beans dumb ass
No, like honestly if you fuck
If you if you try to hurt
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Okay, no, no, no
You're really good friends with a very famous
Transporno, are you?
Who's face
What's the name no one's gonna bother you
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
You know, I bet I you know, I think it's really cool that like you know, I think it's really cool that mr. Bigpipes is like lgbtq
Friendly and it's like, you know, we're not even like you know not just not not a part of the community
But a supporter of the community and you know, proud to have like I'm not really everybody
Mr. Bigpipes
What do you think of Flirty Diamond, Mr. Big Pines?
Because I think you've been in a band with Flirty Diamond.
Yeah, she's cool.
You like her, right?
Like, she's like...
Talk about her, right?
I don't think she's looking for love.
You heard
Like it's like listen to cows moo
Speak your mind bitch speak your mind bitch
Talk to yourself come on dude
Like yeah, this is terrible. I this is really
Different like we have the option to just put our minds together and create a new fucking activity
You're right. Let's do it. Oh, I like that. I like it. Pull it out
You have a better attitude we're all gonna be fun and you're like you keep like, you know
You know, he's going to be a
he's going to forget all about
us. You know, guys, sometimes
there's there's the artist can
be a little bit temperamental.
We don't know. It's talented
artist can be temperamental so
it's okay. Just let me some big
pipes. It's so good. It's so
good. He's a diva. He's acting
like a diva. That's okay.
Musicians. Yeah.
You're a whole diva.
I'll do like a whole deval here
Trivia cards
Oh, yeah, remember we're gonna make our own trivia game one day. I got big dreams for us
You got big what?
Got some big dreams. I got merch got like all kinds of ideas. Oh
Trivia king
Do you guys notice like we play a lot of trivia and a lot of us are actually quite intelligent and
Some in areas that are not but anyways
I'll go on people ask a question and I'll like immediately know the answer to what even think of it
I'm like, how the fuck do I know that?
from trivia playing with you guys
Trivia night
You're smart. It helps. It helps the brain
I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll
I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll
I'll I'll I'll I'll
of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those
What was that shit from somebody started moaning in the middle of something? What was that?
It was like
Some big starting moaning like a like a like a like a girl. Yeah, I think I think it's Canada dry
Doing a reading and I started reading it every time
I really thought it was easy, but like I really thought it was easy. I swear to God
It sounded like easy. I'm not gonna lie to you. It sounded like easy moaning
It wasn't for him. I think I think it was his reading though
Listen, what the robot wasn't he listen, it sounded like his tone of voice
Like he moaned. Oh, yeah, like a like a bitch like yeah, no fuck all that
Somebody else got booty because if it's somebody else got booty, I forgot who it was, but that's right
I think it was ghost
I think maybe go it could have been ghost
That ghost has that Tony whatever it is what it is
Sounded like a woman's voice, but there are no women on the camp, but it sounded really like
Woman or soft-ass dude
Yeah, yeah, that's why I'm saying he had to be easy easy over he talks like that
Assum he says something jelly jelly
But he says that's a little too good. He says it's way too good. Yeah
You got mad experience
Here's a better jelly that I hear you
Don't be jelly
That was definitely stay tuned
I dare you I dare you came up
I bet you a hundred dollars you won't you won't came up and say jelly
Get out the car
Came up and say jelly
I just want you to stay jealous
Hey, hey, hey, no, I want you to come up and say that the fucking
It's so black and dark in here. Sorry. You can't see nothing. That's you know
Sound like you problem. It's not a my problem. It's more like a you problem
You still have two girls saying that word.
You, uh,
coming out of the closet?
Hey, coming out of the closet?
Do you want the baby to know?
I don't say no.
You really want to put that homosexual accent on.
How many of them are wearing diapers?
I think they're mostly wearing diapers.
Well, Mr. Biggs said we're all wearing diapers, we're all wearing diapers, and he likes, I know he likes to project stuff, and I'm just wondering if he's wearing diapers, and then maybe, and I want to see who's wearing diapers.
I'm not wearing diapers.
Everybody wearing diapers? Who the fuck is wearing diapers?
Let's just say mr.
Call us said it said we look we're like lobotomized serial killers and now
Weird shit like
Oh
Because he can't spell
He's in the trail is my pain
I'm telling you no live out of car bum ass nigga can't afford a crib you a bum ass nigga live in Jersey
They live out of the car
I if that's who I want you to think that about
You never showed your bad. You never showed nothing. What you do is show yourself. I'm driving behind a damn car. You live in a goddamn car
I see what if what if that's what I want you to see what if that's like what I want
What if that's the image I want?
It's not
Pussy you sound stupid. This is with an F. How much do you look like mario those stay turn?
There's a Mar-Lewis. Yeah, Memphis. I
Showed you the other days like yeah, I don't want to do it again
I just wondering how you look close to you look like him or no
I've been writing the main chat and then post this comment you're gonna see his picture
Okay
I can't everybody
He's like
like three times as big
Who's his bike? Who's my kid? What's up, dude? Oh guys, that's why you are a gang. I promise you
Guys look you pay that all you can't
Fire yeah, it's like placement trivia. No, you do that. I'll put them all close up. I'm gonna be on the wrong tree
Wrong tree you are
You ain't trying to know anything. Don't do that. Don't do it for yourself.
That's right. Shut up little kid. Don't do it to yourself.
I'll buy that for five bucks.
I'll buy that for five bucks. Let's see. I'm not damn more hammered.
I don't care who you are. You don't gotta be scared.
Or you don't gotta be nobody.
You would have, you would have, you know, you would have a crazy drive.
You came out the closet. You followed me over here. You came out the closet.
Now look at you. You're mad. You're mad. You're mad. Wow.
I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him off, I take him
He did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it, he did it
We get the brown one today better be in a show. Yeah, that way that the white the white feather
Yeah, I was thinking white today white white white the white one. Yeah, that's all right, the Jody. Okay, the Jody rules
Hey listen to him go he's gonna get something going there
You always plays the good shit when we can't hear him. I know I noticed that he's
Weird huh? Yeah
But he's hiding
We are kind of mean I
Mean, but if he is big I think he had people like
You can't say like real old things and it's like and then he got really mad at me
Then he's mad at me. He's mad at me tonight
Then he was those people that weren't doing those saying those terrible things
And I was just
I don't know
Just stop egging soft stop being soft game
I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you for me the other day. We have for me
To the page let's do the stage thing page guy page
No, she's setting something up
Hey, he's got a page. No
Shut up
Get it out of here, right? Yeah, go back take that shit back to the people. Fuck that
It's like me like
I'm gonna respect you psyche and I'm gonna build up and let page talk
I don't need to mute. I'm you know, I'm just gonna be quiet age. You're muted
Yeah, she yeah, he wants to be he wants easy me with shut the fuck up
Okay, yeah
That's all yeah, she's you can strike. Hey, he distracts
She's now getting ready
She's putting the stage together for the ritual
Oh, oh, here we go. I'm wax lighting it now. Very slowly
There's a laugh she laughs okay good. It's all I wanted. It's all I wanted tonight
She's like I said a joke. She looked at me like I was
Uh
Paisie
Wearing denim to Canada is like writing a baby heart writing a Harley and
shedding
Reaver or
spreading a free bird format Angelic nice today though the change jacket in a fitting. Yeah, you got that all great
This is my golf attire today with leggings and Birkin's talks
I'm working for good talks, too
Have you played golf since you went there I
Love golf. That's why I work at the golf course
Say where hey, do they have a ball washing machine?
Yeah, it's going to be you. We're hiring.
You coming down?
Oh, no.
I'm just kidding.
I wonder how many golf balls I could fit in my mouth though. I'd like to try it.
Oh boy!
Listen to how fucking poor they are.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
If you don't know if you don't know that there's a ball washer
Like you obviously don't frequent
I use 100% my mouth every other hole
I'm going to drop in the back where they can't say I'm doing no gay shit. Make it female noises. Oh
Calm down always blame
Like I've just been okay. I have cool friends
Yeah, all right. She's got the feathers now
Of course sometimes
I don't pay for it. I'm by you.
There we go. What is this one?
I don't pay for it. I pick it,
harvest it, and we bless it and
dry it. What? Oh, okay.
Let's get in dry ass. Oh, Austin.
No, let me find your picture.
I'll expose you again to and I'm
going to repeat with this
Oh easy easy Boston don't like you dude
There you go, oh
Here we go. Oh
That's the trophy I feel better
I feel a hundred percent. Thank you, Paige.
Paige, Paige, Paige, Paige, Paige, the rhymes.
You're Nosa.
Yeah, you're right.
She knows it.
Yeah?
What's wrong with you guys? What did you say?
She doesn't, she doesn't what?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Well, I would say that's where you're gonna get pressed take me off the full thing put everybody up there
I hate us. I know this reprise. Why are you talking about me jerking off on pages on it?
Logically for man, and you have a dick, so you probably jerk off like it's
Never done it my time never my entire life if I ever never
What does that word mean I don't know what that word
That's some freak shade. That's some that's some egos none at all
Oh, it's a the antique and that um, what's it? What is the anatomy chair anatomy chair? Cool
What is this? Is this cadaver? It's I think like old medical textbook kind of drawings kind of stuff is it?
Well, let's play trivia. Let's play trivia. I'm drunk as shit. Okay. We're looking at some of my medical textbooks
We should play trivia, but I'll just like show you the cool ones or we'll use them one day. We don't have to do it now
Let's pretend because then everybody's mind is now refreshed and energy is cleansed and so like will not bite
You know or anything or you know, maybe you're not a bit
Okay
That's pretty
Says who's the hippie crying with no camera on? Okay, so that's the bomb got the bomb got blue. That's mr. Big pipes, okay?
Yeah, see who you are too, that's very very page
So all right, what you gotta do is you gotta you you click your AI any of them be like who is mr. Big pipes and it works
I promise. I asked it and it said told me it's not never to ask again
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. I
don't know. I don't know. I
100% I believe you Doug.
Okay, that's cool.
Calming.
It's a calming time.
I can even calm you.
I can poison you, too.
I knew poison was in there somewhere.
Well, I'm a witch.
It's nice on the outside, but it's very dark on the inside.
I was thinking about the cards, actually.
Oh, gotcha.
Well, here it is.
Same thing.
These are so pretty. Okay, continue. I'm just looking. I forgot. I'm dead
Not yet, but one day you will be
Dying
I'll really say you're god. Okay. Good. That's a good thing to the source. Is this your source of two machetes now?
I'm not sure
Yeah, I like the flowers
These people are gonna be like oh that one's cool. I like that one. Is that scissors?
They're all super cool. I don't see two of sorts
Two of sorts. Yeah, just like I like that. Oh, it's okay
They're good observation, uh, got him. I noticed that there's a few a beehive. Okay
Like an Apple watch. I want to see like you should measure your heart rate is doing looks like a brain. Yeah
It's a big house. Let's stay on topic pages. Do a reading, please
How do you know I have medical conditions, Mr. Big Pipe, so you don't have to be so fucking...
Oh, then you could like...
God is God, obviously.
I have a medication for it, it's called nerve damage, I can't help it.
God is God.
Like, you don't have to share with him.
Can you see back screen pictures?
I would just like...
You want to see...
I want to show you my mic.
Interesting.
Yeah, that's alright.
He wants to show me his mic.
Okay, hold on.
I
Got you
It's in the way like when you especially you share your car
There's such a big fucking like artery in your palm there that it like pulses with your heart rate and I can see it
Oh my god, well, he's he's using extra glasses. It's a mr. Big guys. Keep your hand. Keep your eyes on the cards
We'll look at pages palm
It'll especially if you cross your legs if you cross your legs to like in your foot taps. Okay, that's a big toe
Won't you ask to see your lifeline? Why don't you?
That's palm reading that's different type of reading
Palmistry is divination, but it's so nervous like do breathing exercises. Oh my god
I'm not just saying that I just like see you shaking
I'm not going to deny it. So I am. It's what I do.
So maybe like, let's put them together first.
Well, you can throw us some energy.
Miss Midfine, stop bothering Paige. She's trying to do a read.
She's not bothering me.
She's telling you to open and close your leg. I don't know.
I didn't say that. I didn't say that. I said put your hand.
I was saying like, clasp onto it.
I'm just like, let him warm up, let him warm up.
Get it worse, get it worse.
Mr. Raymond is getting creepier and creepier.
I'm trying to save you.
I'm trying to stop him, I'm trying to stop him.
Just ignore it, just ignore it.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Let's try to be real.
Like, we were just playing like,
warm up the cards right now and controlling everything.
The cards are warm, the cards are warm.
That's the drama laugh of the year.
You're taking the laugh of the year of drama.
In these seconds.
At least like, just like, at least that maybe.
Because you're making everyone come
I'm very uncomfortable with mr. Big five disturbing this and God laughing
Shut the fuck up room. All right, we're starting over now. That's how we're doing it
I don't have to be a part that accept tarot cards and
Oh
Yeah, so
Yeah, okay. It's so negative. Same people tell me that I suck a guitar down. Why are you gonna be so negative?
I'm a positive person. I'm a very positive person. You don't know me from a hole in the wall
It's not like it doesn't like, you know
This is worse with me is like I literally I've never spoken to you dude
And you're just telling me all this shit and like that you're insecure
for me
Whoever the fucking dude in the stuff. I just sound like the same shit. Mr. P pipes
Nobody's actually talking to you right now. So you you like you're lost in the source
I'm saying this is a big part. It's like it's like why do you take what do you care what people think?
They say they're bad because you know you're good and then you know, they're not professional guitar players
Why you can't what people say look look guys
You're a terrible person
I never said terrible person
You perceive it as bad
All right, you guys win.
I can't get in the constant straight.
Now it's gonna fall forward, there.
All right, let's go, ready?
Aggressive palms off.
Go ahead, Psyche, go ahead, Psyche, do it.
You want me to do trivia?
I thought that's what you were doing.
I mean, yeah, I have to go on Earth.
Oh my gosh, okay, I got you.
Four hours later.
Okay, okay, so.
What is the circumference of the Earth?
Do you know what is the metric mile?
What is the metric mile?
I should know this.
Nope, this one I don't know.
It's a certain amount of square footage, but it's like how many, what's the number?
You're you're
It's half what God he just said he said it's half of that
300 so I want
Meters. Sorry. No, I said it's quarter miles 1500 meters. You know meters 1500 meters
Wait, that doesn't make sense. I meant it's a metric mile metric is like
of the
the
but we keep a score where we get to 10 wins
but what color what color is Moby Dick what color was Moby Dick black white
great white yes he was right he was white
you got it
not the Moby Dick I'm thinking of
white whale
okay
how many
how many homes stand
where how many what how many okay how many sorry how many uh how many oh my god
wow how many lions stand uh vigil in Trafalgar square oh four uh yes
really like how did you did you really know that
There you go. Is it right? It's it's a wrong answer. Can you explain? I was in the comments. Who left page?
What happened?
What was the answer?
It was it was poor you're gonna right
Oh
Psyche's reading it
Yes, yeah, yeah educated guess was pretty close pretty so is it is just that you guessed for an educated guess. Yeah
Why yeah, he's out of the whole court or something. Well, I want to learn about it. Oh, they're like they're lying
They're guarding all the directions
It's a square so there's one on each side of the square, so
What did I get am I to do I have to write or one right? I forget
I'm not really good at scores, but yeah, we won't we won't pay to win then. We'll just keep playing
How often our brain cells
Often our brain cells replace
Everyday on every fucking 25 years
Seconds
Every one minute
That's huge closer. I'm going 20 years
Or 12 years 12 years, okay
Every two seconds
Actually, it says
0 they're not
I mean once you go dumb, you're that's it
I heard Rado and Bita are also involved in sex trafficking
Someplace games, that's what's up to that
Hey, listen, I am
In I gouges I'm immune to I
Gouges and sex trafficking
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay cuz okay, cuz uh, is saying try to do both to you
No, this is right a sex traffic you
Is that a trivial question cuz I think I think the answer just
Mr. Big I want to hear your sex trafficking story when we were your sex traffic tell me
I mean, I want to hear it. I want to hear it. I need to hear it
I've never been in sex traffic. Oh, okay. I think he still is living in the back of that truck and the person
Like yeah, right. We're here. You got to give some blowjobs to play some music
What's superman or superman name in crypto
I
Dork shit
Dork shit. Oh, it's not dork shit. Dork and look and look and look at they both
What does a nihilist believe in what does a nihilist leave nothing the nihilist nothing. Yes. Yes, the nihilist
okay
Who is who is who is Jerry Jerry Brown's favorite singer?
Any Garcia?
It's a it's a female. It's a female and she's a white female
Okay, her no her name is Linda wrong Linda Ronstadt
Listen to Linda now you don't know see
What is the name of scar what is the name of scar Scarlett O'Hara's what is the name of Scarlett O'Hara's mansion?
I don't know
Was it on Cribs TV? I know this no
It's kind of hard to go on with the wind
Marl, oh with the wind
Okay, okay
Yeah, I don't think it's the right answer the answer is Tara Tara. Oh, yeah
Who who wrote white Christmas?
Think cross behind ours. No, it was it's how you are even Irving Berlin Irving Berlin. That's right. That's right
What is the Chinese book of what is a Chinese book of changes called the Tao?
No, I was gonna say something like that. It's like a
Yeah
What is the brightest planet seen from earth Venus yes, yeah Mars
Well, I got me on the track
What did what street contains the great white way?
the great white way
what street contains the great white way
I don't know what the fuck that is
honky street
it says it is uh
the great white way is in, that's in New York right
I used to make brogs
yeah I think it's Broadway
it's Broadway yes
do you really say frogway?
I said Broadway
I'm drunk, which one you guys typing in the background. I can hear it. I'm not typing
I'm not typing shit. I
Got a shot glass my right hand and some doctor. He's you you know, you're too observant easy. You need to chill
Now my full I got turtle beaches on I got and I got the extra sense on so
What what country was in the 1960 Olympics gold medal in?
I said I wasn't alive in 1960 sorry
What beverage on the what beverage are the what beverage are the flies in and
dip in my
Coke
Sorry, what beverage is the what beverage other and what beverage are the flies and skips in Maloo?
It's strawberry milkshake
lies in
I don't know this one it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's
it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's
Yeah, buttermilks isn't that ranch dress like is there a difference between but like jack in the back
Yeah, I think ranch dressing is buttermilk, but it's like it's really different
But they call it buttermilk and it's not like is who thought of that good jack-in-the-box
No, jack-in-the-box is a shit. They're fucking tacos. They're still 99 cents
They were 99 cents for two and like fucking 2003 dude, and they're still 99 cents for two
What is the what is the highest
hand in straight poker?
Straight plus.
You're on the right track.
It's not a straight flush.
Royal flush.
I got that one.
I got one.
Yeah.
Who is Wilbur?
Mills.
I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never heard of I've never
Yeah, George Reeves. No, no
No Salvador Dali. Yeah, Salvador. That's what I was trying to think of
Yes, yeah, what is it?
What is the strongest muscle there's a strongest muscle in the body?
The tongue tongue is the tongue. Yes. Yes. Uh-huh mission. Uh-huh
Who invented the machine gun in 1862 nickers or Tommy? No, no, no
No, no, no Richard Jason his name is Richard J something but it's awesome
It's Richard J
Gatling this is a Gatling Gatling. Yeah
What uh, what what tools do you use?
To who well
To what what tools do you use to?
Correll C.R.E.W.E.L.L. What?
What are you doing to cruel to something that's I guess it's hard
It says the answer I thought the answer is noodles and cruel noodles I guess noodles. Oh, wow
interesting
I already forgot
Where is the sports of?
Otter tossing originate
Auto tossing
Hello, music. It's fine. It's got to be dead like no, Scotia
He cover CABR cover cover is
There's Scotland I'm not sure. Yeah, that's something over there
What Kennedy what kid what Kennedy was married to to Ethel? Oh
Shit
Robert
Frank
Yeah, what is out of Palmer's what was the answer?
Okay, what was the question?
Yes, it's Bobby Kennedy with Bobby Bobby
Bobby who's Bobby all right wait with a RFK Robert Robert. I think it's Robert. Yeah
Really
what season is statistically the most hazardous
the what what
what season is statistically the most hazardous season
winter
no
summer
it's summer
Where will you find the 20 20 20 moons or 20 20 moons like the grace that you human body
There are 22
I'm sorry, there are 20 moons that grace the human body, there's 24 of these moons.
On the S, there's 20 moons, so what's the answer, so where are they, where are they?
20 moons, the S, let's start with the moon, you mooned me, nope, nope.
That's what they called them. I watched Westwood on HBO and the doctor would be like your moons
But you're gonna have your moons lady to the prostitutes
Moons are the moons are in the brain. There's your periods
No, because there's 20 moons and they are on your fingers. I'm not sure. Yeah, it's so
No, no, no, no, no, no
I did it this morning, but they didn't do 30. I'll show you
You don't got to show face God, but show show your fingers
I'll show. You want to see it?
Yeah, don't change it.
Yeah, we was right. Don't don't don't don't change it. Just just show you now.
Go ahead. Just go ahead. Guys, you know what? What what guys, what what
what plants did St. Patrick use to explain the trinity?
Yes
God damn
Shamrock but it usually has three three days okay, so what's saying did personal level discover?
Well, Pluto a web planet what planet did personal low discover?
Oh
Yeah, it's a pseudo and then pseudo might not be a plant. I don't think they're out of date
Guys, you know who eloped with the pussycat
Tom John eloped the pussycat. No, it's okay. It's okay. It's like a
Oh, um, um, uh, what's how's it go? Um, little boy blue
And the Jew
Jack's proud could eat no fat. No, it's all the and the cow jumped over the moon. The
It's called it's called a blank
It's called a blank and
And the pussy cat blank and the pussy cat so what so I am always
The pussy cat was not married to the spoon. She's not uh, not Michael Leguiz mom. Oh, well, Jody in the pussy cat
No, Jody. Yeah, I'm Jody in the pussy cat. Jody are sleepy. No
No, Jody
No, I'm very wise wise wise
No, it's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It's not. It
Yeah, the owl
Actually, you know at the bird I heard the owl doesn't even have the largest brain, I mean
Are you talking shit about the owl dude
And I think and I think Raven those martyrs in them, too
Okay, uh beautiful. Mm-hmm. Did I don't stop scratch? Look what you started legs. Put them away. We need your feet to be
No, no feet pics. No. I'm page. Are you into dark humor? Yeah. So sometimes I don't like like I don't like it.
They're not like yeah, I was watching videos of it earlier. It was I'm not gonna say nothing cuz it's
What's you the face cards like cows and Jen Rummy. Oh my god
What do the base cars count to in Jin Ramy?
Page.
If we were like, if we were chilling you wouldn't you wouldn't have to shave your armpits around me
Lovely, no, but
I'm sure you liked it. That was the whole thing because the person
Made it a thing because I didn't never mind. We're not to why are we making? I'm not making the thing right now. Continue trivia
Psyche really likes armpits. Psyche's always asking me to show my armpits and shit, and I'm like, I don't really get it
well people like
Yeah, but you're supposed to talk about pages. It's all I supposed to be you're my thing
Well, no, I think it's cool. Like if I like I think our pits are okay like
Okay, if a girl wants to like not shave her armpits, I think it's fucking I like dig the confidence
I because I think if I was a girl like would I give a fuck like I'd be like goddamn. I'm fucking
Work hard enough to be fucking
Fucking hot enough because I work hard. I'm gonna be fucking hot enough. I fucking I fuck hot dudes or whatever
So I'm gonna fucking let my heart
Just heard that psyche I heard
No, I was saying if I was a chick, with armpit hair.
Oh, why would you imagine yourself as that?
Because that's how I would rule, that's how I would rule.
If I had a fucking daughter, I'd be like, bitch, don't shave
your legs.
Oh, no, OK.
There's a big one in the police.
Why would you do that?
Let me come up.
Because who gives a fuck?
Who the fuck cares?
Like.
If you're fucking like you have your dollar girls like what you want to you want to make someone feel bad because they grow hair
Other fucking armpit
We were sideways like that that was the weirdest thing with the undone that was literally go
What
I wouldn't
Because I'd be like shit. I'm gonna fucking work hard and be hot enough that like
We're gonna work hard there and we really need this
Shave those things. I mean, you're sweating dude. I would respect like if I respect like
Who you are as a person I don't give a fuck about your fucking arm. Hey, I'd be like fuck you have fucking dorks
Everyone
I don't judge you but you know
Each is own
What county is Chicago?
You know what County Chicago
It's in a county in Chicago
In County fucking date. No, it's my um Chicago is
I I don't know it. I like I fucking know it. I don't know it fucking songs. I don't know. I don't know capitals
It's in Cook County. Yeah, I cook County Jail
Yeah
Okay, let's see
Candyman took place in Chicago
Yeah, who who is Leslie Boke Leslie Bogart's mother who Leslie Bogart's mother was oh no
Leslie Bogart's mother
Yeah, it's a lower. Her name is Lauren McCall Lauren McCall. I don't know who that is
She's like a very kind of like a mask. I got more masculine. She's kind of like a cat's internal type a little bit. Okay
How long do we have?
Yeah, I think I've been through the pile
How many colors out there in a rainbow?
Roy G boo
Yeah, right there's seven. Yes
And then in double rainbows they invert
That's what's gonna get out. Okay. That's cool. So like he needs a new um a new deck a new um question thing
Hey, we got so much so much here
We should all buy a new trivia game. Good morning. I just woke up. Good morning. Oh, you can hear it in your voice. Good morning
Mr.. Big Pets you remember some of it
So because you remember summer mr. Big Pets, maybe I'm Kentucky
One of those girls had like the shape of the implants. Oh my god
She's you haven't seen my team so you wouldn't know if I have implants or not
No, you're talking about like Kid Rock and like you know, I don't know no wrong bitch
Stop doing so much fucking shit and maybe you can keep up with people
What?
I know it's you're always
Get on get on the fucking shit and play trivia and beat me in trivia. No, I play in trivia
I didn't come up to play trivia. I came up to fuck with you
I'm gonna put some beers in the freezer VRB. All right. Good. Thanks. That'd be great
What's up everybody?
I'm good, so I crashed when I got home last night. I was four out busy week
Yeah, there's a really there's a summer solstice yet on the 21st and so it was like a really intense energies
I think going on and I think a lot. Yeah, that's my day
Right and I think right now
Sorry my bad, what'd you say? No, no, it's fine
Like we're going but it's also y'all I think some people seem to kind of like hiding emotions and because we're going it's 21st transfers in the cancer season and cancers
Ruled by them by the moon and water and so that is like a motion
And so I think it maybe is an intensely emotional time of year for a lot of people. I saw a lot of people going through it
in the last few days, you know
There's a lot going on in the world. Yeah
Yeah, okay, so some of you seen you make these I have some drawings. I did I want to draw you too
I said, oh you asked if I draw it was right today or not. Do you see some of the drawings? I'm not sure
I didn't draw some people. I do no tj. Electra through uh, I do you got any?
She's my best friend
Like to the Electra here
No, I don't like it. Oh, yeah. Oh, you don't like her. Well, she is. You think I do exactly what that bitch looks like to
Say, hey, sir
Good job. Now here's Gotti your guy
Yeah, that's like Gotti. Yeah, that's not I do the I drew a moon and a sun
But it's pretty I took a boot banana and a donut magically. Okay, and then I
drew I do rogue nomad. It's kind of like from the
It looks like
It's big nicer or her or alias rogue. No matter. Okay, and then we have you know, do you want to be easy?
Yes, let me see easy
Yep
Yeah, that looks like easy
You know what it's easy here to see you know they see the wolf man
Oh, yeah, okay. Well, yeah, I know you're talking about now. Yeah. Okay. I've never seen him but that looks about right
This is I don't know if you know this is dingle. This is dingle. They're in the chat
This is just their avatar the dingles in the chat. I drew. Yes. It looks like a dingleberry. That looks good. Yeah, that works
You know, do you know the sassy scarlet?
Yes, I'm not sassy
Okay, I like the hat you got that you gotta go devil
I got a lasso with the heart in it and a pitchforker. Oh, okay. I thought that was a devil sort
My bad. Oh, hey, buddy. He's a very large
I do I try to do a cowboy had turned out into late like a one of those like a
Omnist or something. I'm not sure
Came out a little and you know time. It's beautiful. I'm sure she appreciates it. Yeah time. I know time
Time there's time
There you go. There you go
This is gonna be all the artwork that's going in his book that he's gonna be putting out people to say y'all know
Yes, funky
Spunky with the guys friend and
You ever seen her she was on the show a couple last couple days, but I'll show you every see you when he goes
Here's goes as you go see
There you go, if you guys enjoy those productive today
Yeah
Let's sum it is my picture. Oh, this is the one he copy. I was like cuz he's like put a picture up
I'm gonna draw it and I put I bet it's the way where you're holding the coconut. Yeah
I cook and I put the drink
I'll try to make it easy for him. He's like, yeah, I want that one. I'll die right
I like that glass
From the restaurant I kept it
Yeah, it was long I was good
Yeah, I can't drink those listen
I'm I am I can smoke bud like I can smoke weed all day long
I smoke weed all day long
I can drink a strawberry daiquiri and bitch. I am twisted. Do you understand cuz I don't drink so
I'll every now and then me and my husband will go out and I'll be like filling myself
I'm like, well, I'm gonna get to strawberry daiquiri and like I'll literally drink half of it and get up and my husband's like, babe
You're you're kind of weevil wobbling a little bit. Are you good?
Okay
Oh, yeah, he'll just kind of he'll just laugh cuz I get you know, I mean I'm fine when I'm drunk
So that's the good part unless somebody like truly pisses me off as I'm really like fun
I like to get topless when I'm drunk. So that's probably why I don't drink a whole lot
So is summer's fun at a party
Oh, yeah, well, I might find her drunk that I am sober I can promise you that
Cuz I don't think about shit, you know what I mean? I'm just like, oh, there's that sexy lady. Look at her. She's so beautiful
Oh
Yeah, well, mr. Bigfives like uh, he's good, right?
Well, mr. Bigfives, I think mr. Bigfives he was he was asking about her armpits and they say he was a woman he would
Is your stream yard being weird the last like week
It has been it it has been a little weird
I think they're doing some updates or something because on all my pages. I've been having a little weird shit
Yeah, I host a live and it was telling me 404
Nobody
He's my friend bought me some weed tonight so I can smoke out of the bomb now. Oh, yeah
Oh, we got the weed tips are nice. I hope it all spoke as we speak. I'm spoken as we speak
Yeah, that's a little like some nice green that's how I like my we that bright green like that like like green right that with the red strands in it
I love it. Yeah
Rich like red. Yeah, those are my favorite ones
My time yellow, but it smells really good. This is a pretty good way
Was it but on the vape thing for like three or four months for weed vapes make me cough
That's why my voice be a little rough right now because I was we was out somewhere and I couldn't smoke
So I started hitting a vape and now my voice is just all fucked up
Yep, that happens to me and with raw paper. I could smoke bamboo of raw paper. I
Get it like it itching it back with my throat and I just can't smoke it
Think I'm going to switch my paper. It's like I smoke blood. So I'm just used to smoking blunts
You know what I mean, but like I don't know the papers getting on my nerves
So I think I'm gonna
That bamboo stuff I heard it's good
Yeah, I could fuck with but raw. I can't I
Don't like rolling papers cuz like they just go out so much. I mean I'd be sucking it, but it just be going out
Oh my god, somebody somebody made fun to be there was like, you know, you smoke it on the same look for like three hours
I was like, yeah, keep going
At least somebody caught that page
Right
You look gorgeous today by the way. You kind of kick you fell off
He said I'd be sucking it and I said of course you heard that limb dick
You do be so good. Don't you I want to name my
Paper she pulled out a roll paper. Yeah, I can't standals. No, you said I be something like hey
Let me ask you a question. Hey dumb nuts decline page. Can I ask you a question?
So how do you get up from stopping like burning and stuff like like you know what I mean?
Like it just sometimes I'll get it. Oh, I mean I roll it good and everything and it just it either always goes out or run
I'd think that I'm with you on like the hey these just have a natural like adhesive or whatever gum for the
The rolling cart and I feel like really seal goods and I don't know it just kind of like burns away from itself
Right, I do not like my way. Thank you taking it ahead in the bank for me. Please. Yeah
Okay, but I can like hold it up like real quick and then I can do it kind of off camera a little bit and then
Oh, I like that. Hold on wait before you hit it. Let me see
I like it. It's cute. I'm about to get me another. I'm about to buy me a
bong. I haven't had it. I like it. That's cute. I like that. Thank you.
It's an easy, easy sponsored response to me. So, thank you so much.
He's a good guy. He takes care of his friend.
He helps me with the outreach from time to time. I know he probably didn't want me to say that my bad
I was just about to write in the back
My bad, I'm sorry
But every now then he needs to be notarized for the good shit that he does because he gets a fuck a bad rap all the time
And he's been doing really good and I'm really proud of him
Really proud of you easy. I've been watching and you know, I'm always watching I'm my big sis and like in alley creeps
Like how you do it, but you really been doing your shit. I'm proud of you
Let's try my best. You're not falling for the dumpship and you know every now and then we do it's all good
But like you haven't seen it for working
Well, I feel like you need to be acknowledged
Because I'll be real quick when you fucking up be like I damn it. So I want to be also real quick
When you see I be I was like, I was trying to say the way you say I be I wanted to name my son
profan
Oh my god
Name this you can name there is a bunch of names. You can't name King
Susan it still looks like Jesus if that's really what you wanted to do
Yep, my art you so he's called me baby Jesus
That fucking hair here. That's probably why I wouldn't
Dude my listen, this is the first year I have had like all my hair is finally it's finally growing out
My line is ibuprofen and it is so fucking hot
My god, I want to I want to grow my hair down to my like middle of my like how long pages is like a little bit longer than that
No, I got my hands. I got to cut my hands. You should I was looking at them. They all fucked up
Nice pepper actually, I'm really proud of myself dude
Like my hair like I've been using a lot of different things to put like just treatments and shit on my hair
And my hair is like fucking super healthy right now
Which I love
I love my alone. Okay, baby
I've had I've been so used to it being short and shaved and all that shit like now
I have this long hair and it's so my hair so fucking thick. It is so
Well
Can we talk a little bit it's a big pass. We're chillin
I
Been busy as fuck so I like like hanging out for a little bit
Yeah
That's who you are you miss very much. So yeah, remember you on with summer like recently and like you recognize your Kentucky accent and stuff
You you're kind of gonna
Bright red hair, you know who I am
I'll take a picture from one of my lives just now. Oh my god. Thank you one of my lives. Yeah, that's me
One of my life. He's got long answer
He's got that good Hispanic long thick hair
Okay, okay, like you like a Hispanic guy from fluid Mac or something give it if you were back here. I like it tell me
You know, it's good
He does
Are you seeing are you seeing?
Like like someone did a compliment of their work and stuff, but that's a bad picture. I just took it right now
It was a fast one
Yeah, you hear you like yeah, like I wasn't focused like you just like fucking I'm picturing like some like
Yeah, you'll get a lighter
They go over plant. Oh now I'm getting like vitality and Chris Hansen vibes. Oh
That's not good
No, but that's real
Easy there Chris Hansen vibes
You know me times I got I got stopped in a shit Jose Jose. I'm my name's not Jose. Oh shit
Yeah, you look just like my friend. I'm gonna go. Yeah, it's going there
Let's get him stronger
What's that? What are you talking about? What's getting stronger? What's getting up? Whoa? Whoa?
in vibes
Wait, oh, he's a Chris Hansen
Here I'm pure Chris Hansen good. I could be something by please
Okay
Oh, we put the allegedly saw back up
You know you say a letter jelly
Thank you
Your big pipes does does a thing that's that shit is hot though. Don't think about it the man
Don't like it. It's really I don't know man. It's really not that cool. She's come cool though
It's not that cool.
That's who it's like you say.
You know, this is going to be kind of corny, I get it.
But like, you know, all my babies are grown now.
And it's so funny because like my youngest daughter,
she's working now, right?
So instead of waking her up for school and shit,
like I'm waking her up to put a job.
Ah, enjoy your little ones people. I know this ain't the place to talk about kids, but sorry
Little fuckers
When you call her you say I bet you used to call still call about a little nickname gave him what she was two or three
Oh, yeah, she's thinking about all day long
And my son he'll be popping until he's fucking 30 90 years old. You know what I mean? Like I don't
So fucking dumb
You're rude in my tits my chat if you're calling us all dumb you see he already said that
On the panel sign like it was the bottom eyes
What's up? What's up? What's up?
What's up? What's up?
Who called anyone an idiot? No one called anyone. You did. No, I didn't rewind
Again admit when you're wrong are you gonna admit when you're right when you
I'm looking for my other phone right now admit when you're wrong
Well, let's play it. I mean, I was so I'm sure to remember, but I
Who's that? Yeah, I believe that people in a chat
And I believe I do
Yeah, oh
Come on
Are you going to sing with me?
Yeah!
We've got money
Oh yeah
If only you would have made it
We don't have a puff.
Sing it, Sanky.
Sing it, baby.
Oh, my God.
Last time I heard Burdo or whatever was on, and for the first time I was able to actually
hear them, and then, you know, of course, it, you know, but I think I kept up with them
a little bit.
I was like, but I think I've been there.
It was fun.
And I ain't talking shit.
They're actually kind of, all right.
It was kind of cool.
Yeah, I think they got mad at me at the end, but it's okay. I'm not I don't care
But look Paige it was the first time I actually got to like understand what that was like wow
This is kind of cool. It's like I've never heard. I'm talking normal. You know to me or you know come somewhat normal
Gotta be on on beat us
Yeah. Yeah, the one that talks real fast. I
Understand when he talks like that. That's crazy
Well, I do too. That's the crazy thing
But it was cool to hear him which by our brains are just fucked up. That's why but it was cool to hear her
I'm sorry because she's trans. I want to make sure I identify
It was cool to hear her
Just talk like somewhat normal like I mean it was still super fast, but who's trans?
We're doing diamonds continue with it. Yeah, somebody else
Summer like mr. Big Five's is like very trans friendly he likes this trans in Lena Horan their friends and
He's I think he's open to your mentee are you?
I
Like a case-by-case basis. Oh
Thank you, you'll appreciate so we had our pride parade the other day, right?
And you know my shirt that says I love Peggy Min
Well, I wore that with a pair of Daisy Dukes and honey my shirt was a hit them Queens love that shirt, baby
They was like
Oh, yeah, talking about that talking about the parade right there was guys out there with the Speedos
Yeah
I mean, my booty cheeks was out. I have booty shorts on.
I said, oh, look, look, speedos.
These guys got speedos.
Oh, shit.
They can go love it.
That's the one place that you can, like, wear, you know,
whatever, inside of it, Joe.
I've only been pegged once.
Oh.
I think you've been pegged.
I could tell.
I like pegged people, though.
I could have been pegged.
I'll tell you, I was really high on heroin.
I was really high on heroin.
And of course the chick that did it was like so fucking hot
What size was the strap on it was an experimental thing how big was the strap on?
How big was the strap on like how large what did you have inserted?
Well, there's like it started out with a a small one and then went on to like a butt plug
But plug I think I still have it to actually oh my god
You look so beautiful tonight. I like that. It looks really good on you
Look at this dude geeking out
Did that shake go down?
He's like in love with me. It's so weird
What shit? Oh, it went down. It went in and out and down and up
The butt plug?
No, not the bullet pump
That yeah, we understand that
You see a small like a small
Yeah, it probably wasn't much bigger than this like Dr. Pepper
So what did you do?
Dr Pepper bottle is pretty much the, and that's a lot to take on me.
Personally, it's probably like the first rib of the Dr Pepper, and then it tapered off
like after that.
But I mean, it got, it got in there.
Take it, Dr Pepper dude.
You're a fucking champ.
Okay.
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
Here's a bodybuilder
Strong yeah, I don't know like she's definitely like a like really fit
Yeah, like one of the strongest fucking yeah, I would say absolutely the strongest woman I've ever
I get it like I mean trying to like we would actually like
train together and shit and
I get it our sports and stuff and you really go at it and
Like she is really strong. Probably just yeah, she's the strongest woman. I've ever dealt with
Yeah, if you are muscles who would who would win no destroyer, but she's so be strong. Oh my god, okay
I've never lost to a woman arm wrestling. It's terrible, but yeah,
I've been doing this shit for like, since I was a teenager.
Take a more
At arm wrestling
Well, I'm really glad I'm that's I love that for you that you beat women arm wrestling as your party trick
Okay, I want against every woman
How many men, all right, you ran over 300 women, right?
How many men?
How many men, have I been arm wrestling?
Yeah, honest, honest, honest answer.
Probably like most of them, I don't know.
Most of them. Yeah, like like 99% see a record. Okay, so you see what you see well
How many how many times this if you're done and how many how many young women how many like that's like what?
Well, what was the arm wrestling like how does that come about with it that you can almost lose?
Yeah, I mean they have zero minute men have beat me arm wrestling
Yeah, but no, no, I've never had one beat me arm wrestling
Okay, okay, okay. Let's get back to the butt plug. Okay, so that was the only toys and then okay
Are those the only toys?
You know hey, dude, if you're gonna go in like this
No, like you need a five-gallon first of all you can't mention that around psyche guess happy. Look how happy you got him
He's not making fun of you. He's curious
No, I'll make money. You need to spray a little bit. And just
Turn me off
Did she go straight in on you he's actually like he's thinking about it
You don't want that. Everybody's curious. I'm so
fucking good. We just want to know because we love it.
We're having a great time. We're having fun laughing. What's
the problem? I don't know but. Here's my goodie kitty.
Five-dimensional dick pic chest. Figure it out. Dick pic
Why does it sound like anime to me for some reason? I don't know why I'm thinking. Is that the wrong thing? It's weird
The only chest I know about it's a milky and chest, but it's very very complicated
You better shoot it
What's up, I said all I know is like you got a shot and you better shoot it
Okay
So like we could probably talk about anything else now too because we're over this for now, right? Yeah, I'm a real
page
Yeah, I'm like you can tell here. Yeah. Yeah. Hey, no, no, you have to page real quick
I'm being so rude. I'm being so rude. I'm being so rude. Sorry Canadians say it like that rude. How do you say sorry?
Like I'm sorry for being as drunk as I am and I want to be really nice
But I'm too drunk to like be able to act this way. I think yeah, you don't say sorry like a Canadian
Like you say sorry say it how you say it
Sorry
Sorry, I know that you are I'm not making ever see I just made everybody
She all into apologizing for
Imagine like you'd like to give me like just like nothing but like denim panties on
Some
Put that jacket like around your crotch
I
You need to make some we have a bottle ranch truss in here. Okay, drink the bottle of red chestnut with us and hang out
What's up?
Who's gonna buy psyche a sequin speedo and a denim speedo now is on the bucket list, right?
Thanks
That'll be those sounds cool. We play look they still denim their pants
When I used to ride bikes a lot I used to have some dope ass check leather champs. Oh, what kind of bikes did you ride?
motorcycles
Obviously
Carly's I mean, I mean really anything. I like bikes period. I don't like crotch rocket stuff sincerely, but I'll ride them
Like I'm all you look like you like to read
Yeah, you're as I've only got it. I was it was great
What that you like to ride dick
Oh riding dick doesn't make you uncomfortable riding motorcycles does oh, okay
Never mind. I was gonna ask a question, but I'm not gonna know
No, cuz the stupidest thing I've ever said
Right in a bag chat, there's no
The only question that stupid is a question not asked
They
Question it was just kind of like a page thought and then picture to my brain
You can't you can't well, I don't I mean I've done a motorcycle before but not why I was going
Probably I'm sure of it. There's somebody's done it
There you go. Yeah, like I'm yeah, I've had sex on a bike, but it wasn't we were on the side of the road
Is the big part you got packed on the bike before
Not
Over or is there other things involved and like how many did you put in and
Did she do anything or
Okay, yeah, there's so many questions
I'm really not interested.
You don't have to.
It's just, like, honestly, him just getting excited to talk about it.
Oh, why not make you uncomfortable as many fucking people
as you make uncomfortable?
I want the answer, but let's fucking go.
The series on Showtime is called Steven Spielberg.
You fucked Steven Spielberg?
The Showtime series.
Oh, it's called The United States of Terra.
And I was doing like a shit ton of heroin with this like super hot stripper chick and
We were watching that shit
Oh, is that what she pegged you to?
United States of Terra. We'd like sleep for like
18 hours and wake up about
But yeah, at one point we were like, I don't know. We're probably fucking
Actually, I think we're like closed out my apartment
Cuz we're moving to another apartment as we're just being up like let's fucking get this place clean like we're up for like
Fucking like a long time
Yeah, I'm getting pegged into it Harold. I'm sure you was up for a while. Yeah, it was even that it was like I
Say like the whole like sex session of pegging probably only lasted like maybe like two hours or something. Oh my god
All right
You got you got a booty on you, baby
You just can everybody all up in here worked up look at psych look at look at look at all my friends. Look what you've done to them
She wants the attention to always be on you so we're giving you the attention you're an attention or it's okay
I want to say it's disgusting. I mean, I'm sure you guys know it's not disgusting. I love pick-a-man, but I'm just saying
To me it's embarrassing because it's like I'm shy there's nothing about you embarrassing you're up here. You come on, dude, really
You're not very shy, this is the attention you all you're looking for so we're giving it to you shut the fuck up
you're not gonna like I'm
This is my private life
But then he said it was like a nine. It was like a nine inch. Oh, no, he said a can of
Yeah, he said he said a doctor by a dr. Pepper bottle entire dr. Pepper
A bottle
He said bottle because I was like god damn
I gotta go. Thank you. Dr. Pepper bottle now. Hold on
With your legs behind your head or were you very bent over on your knees on the bed?
That would definitely hurt like page like I mean, I don't even yeah, no, I'm good
Even in the even in the JJ that would fucking be like, oh my god
I know look page. I swear to God look I'm up looking for I'm looking for a bottle
Psyche's got the pictures. I'm in my underwear. He's got the pictures you can share
You figure a dr. Pepper bottle bigger than this
You'd need to let you have my permission
Like a you have my permission to
Okay, okay. Thank you. You can let people judge from that
Just I just like I don't know if I feel comfortable
Setting your people pictures of you you and your underwear like I don't I don't want no pictures sense of being underwear
Well, I mean it's you can get it. You can get an idea of
You know, I know I don't know we're not asking how little your dick is we're asking how loose your ass is because you said
Dr. Pepper bottle up the ass
Eight inches eight inches. It's eight inches. Eight inches. You got something
Oh my god, okay. Hey, that's pretty good
Let me tell me
No, yeah, yeah eight inch strap on you got paid to the eight inch a two-hour straight. Let's watch it
You're a legend dude, cuz I sure the fuck and I can't say
You know, I'm a freak but I don't know about all that one. I think I might have to step out on that one
I ain't really down I guess
Yeah
No, we don't want to see you in your order that has nothing to do with the coke bottles going up your ass
The fuck is that got to do with that? Oh, I'm sorry. Dr. Pepper bottle. Yeah, it kind of does look like a duck gets a soda, right?
I know let me correct it.
Dr. Pepper
Got a story split. You better have that lid on tight cuz that's a spicy leak
all right
I'll say like now. I know why his name is mr. Big Pipe's cuz he took big pipes
The way I feel about my guitar playing and a bandro playing, I kind of feel about my guitar too, so what's up?
Well, I mean, Psyche might want to, you know, let Psyche hit it.
That's not through talent. That's like through genetics and shit. I can't...
You're sitting here. We're talking about getting stuck in your ass. You want to talk about your dick?
Let me know that you really don't have a big dick.
I hate to practice so shit fucking time.
Let me know that you don't have a big dick.
Should we get a guitar and banjo and like, I'm trying to...
But we're trying to get psyche some ass, so you're gonna like...
You have to brush your teeth
Your best is like so he needs to brush his as much as he fucking drinks. It's good that you care about
Like some hygiene is important
Yeah, and then he said take a shower and then I was like
You're talking about that moment that's probably what I was saying. I was being real
Then I let him back several minutes later and then he says
if your show enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter enter
Hey, those here, you guys need some rbf here. It's not rbf for you guys
There's a baby man took off run under cycle right now. They're playing so that so they get the people that